<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>EN - Ecommerce blog by PrestaShop</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2016 16:43:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.8.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>6 New Year&#8217;s Resolutions for 2016 from the PrestaTeam</title>
		<link>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/6-new-years-resolutions-2016-prestateam/</link>
		<comments>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/6-new-years-resolutions-2016-prestateam/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2016 17:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kate Robinson]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce Tips and Advice]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/?p=21008</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>It’s a new year, which means it’s time to start new habits that will make you a better&#8230;well, you. We asked around the office to see what resolutions the PrestaTeam is making. Here are 6 that every merchant can adopt. We promise, they’re easier to keep than that fancy new diet you read about on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/6-new-years-resolutions-2016-prestateam/">6 New Year&#8217;s Resolutions for 2016 from the PrestaTeam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en">EN - Ecommerce blog by PrestaShop</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It’s a new year, which means it’s time to start new habits that will make you a better&#8230;well, you. We asked around the office to see what resolutions the PrestaTeam is making. Here are 6 that every merchant can adopt. We promise, they’re easier to keep than that fancy new diet you read about on Buzzfeed.<br />
<span id="more-21008"></span></p>
<h2 style="color: #cf763a">1) Make new friends.</h2>
<p>It seems that as we get older, we make less time for making new friends. So in 2016, we vow to turn off our computers, put down our phones and get out and meet new people! We’re going to join MeetUp.com, attend PrestaShop community events, and say “yes” to the next invitation we receive. It’s a great way to practice our social skills and maybe even make some new friends. Who knows? If you try it too, you might just meet your next business partner!<br />
<strong><a href="https://www.prestashop.com/preston/" target="_blank">Preston &#8211; PrestaShop Mascot</a></strong></p>
<h2 style="color: #cf763a">2) Take a vacation.</h2>
<p>Entrepreneurs, let’s just admit it: we’re workaholics. Our drive to solve everyday problems makes us successful at our business. But this year, we’re going to put the problem solving on hold for a bit. We’re hitting the road. Whether it’s taking short cruise or driving the length of Route 66, we’re determined to see another part of the world. Although it may feel like time taken away from our business, we’re going to use it as time to refuel and maybe even come up with some new ideas for the company.<br />
<strong><a href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/author/julieliu/">Julie Liu</a> &#8211; Marketing Specialist </strong></p>
<p>Need inspiration? Check out all the <a href="https://www.pinterest.com/prestashop/meet-preston/" target="_blank">cities our mascot</a>, Preston has visited in 2015!</p>
<h2 style="color: #cf763a">3) Adopt a pet.</h2>
<p>Having a dog may seem counterintuitive: do you really need more responsibility? But having someone else depend on you also gives you motivation to get your life in order: get up early every morning (forget about sleeping until noon), eat at reasonable meal times, get home at a decent hour&#8230;establishing a regular rhythm will help you keep your store on track as well. And best of all, you&#8217;ll get plenty of love all day long, which will decrease stress levels and boost your morale when you&#8217;re filling out all your product data sheets!<br />
<strong><a href="https://www.prestashop.com/forums/user/1117607-sylvain-dermy/" target="_blank">Sylvain Dermy</a> &#8211; Community Manager</strong></p>
<h2 style="color: #cf763a">4) <a style="font-family: 'Roboto Condensed',Tahoma,Verdana,sans-serif;font-size: 28px;font-weight: 300" href="https://www.prestashop.com/en/training-prestashop">Learn something new!</a></h2>
<p>There’s a saying that you can’t teach an old dog new tricks. Well, thank goodness you’re not a dog. <img src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif" alt=":)" class="wp-smiley" />  With such a wide variety of online resources available, it’s easier than ever to learn something new. We suggest <a href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/7-free-ways-to-learn-how-to-code-like-an-ecommerce-developer/">learning how to code</a>. Not only will you start to understand what your developer is saying, but you might be able to squash some bugs on your website yourself!<br />
<strong>Danny Moreno &#8211; Technical Support</strong></p>
<h2 style="color: #cf763a">5) Be more Social &#8211; online that is.</h2>
<p>Have you abandoned your social media followers in the midst of the holiday rush? This year, we’re committed to speaking and listening to our fans! Although we can’t say “‘yes” to everything, we’re going to say it as much as we can. It’s important that we build a good relationship with our fans, and not just continuously promote our products. We’re passionate about what we sell, and that’s what we want to share with our fans.<br />
<strong><a href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/author/kate/">Kate Robinson</a> &#8211; Content Manager</strong></p>
<h2 style="color: #cf763a">6) Make no resolutions.</h2>
<p>Let’s be realistic for once: no one keeps their resolutions. Why not sell exercise equipment in the first week of January, and then snack foods for the rest of the year. Now that’s what we call understanding your customers. <img src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif" alt=":)" class="wp-smiley" /><br />
<strong>Brenna Verner &#8211; Merchant Success Specialist &#8211; <a href="http://addons.prestashop.com/" target="_blank">PrestaShop Addons</a> </strong></p>
<hr align="left" width="20%" />
<p>How do you plan on improving in 2016? Let us know in the comments below! and most importantly…</p>
<h2 style="color: #cf763a"><strong>Happy 2016 from the PrestaShop family! </strong></h2>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/6-new-years-resolutions-2016-prestateam/">6 New Year&#8217;s Resolutions for 2016 from the PrestaTeam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en">EN - Ecommerce blog by PrestaShop</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/6-new-years-resolutions-2016-prestateam/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>A look back at 2015</title>
		<link>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/look-back-2015/</link>
		<comments>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/look-back-2015/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2016 17:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Julie Liu]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[PrestaShop News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/?p=21053</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>2015 has been an amazing year for everyone at PrestaShop. Join us as we take stock of last year and prepare for an even more eventful, international and profitable 2016! 5,000,000 downloads of PrestaShop. We would not have reached this milestone without you &#8211; our community! From everyone at PrestaShop, we thank you for your [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/look-back-2015/">A look back at 2015</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en">EN - Ecommerce blog by PrestaShop</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2015 has been an amazing year for everyone at PrestaShop. Join us as we take stock of last year and prepare for an even more eventful, international and profitable 2016!</p>
<p><span id="more-21053"></span></p>
<hr />
<br />
<img src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2016/01/look-back-2015-0-1024x537.jpg" alt="look-back-2015-0" width="700" height="367" class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-21058" /></p>
<h2 style="text-align: center; font-weight: 700">5,000,000</h2>
<p><a title="Download PrestaShop" href="https://www.prestashop.com/en/download" target="_blank">downloads of PrestaShop</a>. We would not have reached this milestone without you &#8211; our community! From everyone at PrestaShop, we thank you for your continued support of our open source project and the countless contributions (no matter how big or small) you’ve made.</p>
<hr />
</p>
<p><img src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2016/01/look-back-2015-1.jpg" alt="look back 2015-1" width="657" height="345" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-21062" /></p>
<h2 style="text-align: center; font-weight: 700">$1,000,000</h2>
<p>That’s how much we’ve dedicated to helping PrestaShop developers around the world develop better localized features for all merchants. Learn more about our Integration Fund and how you can participate.</p>
<hr />
</p>
<p><img src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2016/01/cat.gif" alt="cat" width="400" height="400" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-21067" /></p>
<h2 style="text-align: center; font-weight: 700">17,683+</h2>
<p>pictures taken of Puff. He can’t help being fluffy, puffy and cute &#8211; and we can’t help taking pictures of him. <a href="https://twitter.com/puff_life" target="_blank">Follow him on Twitter</a> to see what it’s like to be an office cat.</p>
<hr />
</p>
<p><img src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2016/01/look-back-2015-3-1024x537.jpg" alt="look back 2015-3" width="700" height="367" class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-21064" /></p>
<h2 style="text-align: center; font-weight: 700">2,000</h2>
<p>attendees showed up for <a href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/prestashopday-recapping-amazing-event/">PrestaShop Day</a> in Paris. The overwhelming support for our event, despite the heat, made us the trending topic in France twice in a day. <a href="http://www.prestashopday.com/en/" target="_blank">Check out the list of workshops and events</a> we offered!</p>
<hr />
</p>
<p><img src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2016/01/look-back-2015-4.jpg" alt="look back 2015-4" width="657" height="345" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-21065" /></p>
<h2 style="text-align: center; font-weight: 700">50</h2>
<p>modules are now under development, thanks to funding from our <a href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/takes-apply-integration-fund-get-share-1-million/">Integration Fund</a>. We’re still looking for more payment gateways, shipping modules, marketplace connectors and admin tools. Have an idea for a module you’d like to develop? <a href="http://ambassadors.prestashop.com/application-form" target="_blank">Apply today</a> to see if we can help you kickstart your module development.</p>
<hr />
</p>
<p><img src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2016/01/01.png" alt="01" width="516" height="275" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-21066" /></p>
<h2 style="text-align: center; font-weight: 700">24 &#8211; 15 &#8211; 22</h2>
<p>24 Ambassadors in 15 countries and 22 cities: earlier this year, we kicked off an <a href="http://ambassadors.prestashop.com/" target="_blank">Ambassador Program</a> as our way to reward and support PrestaShop enthusiasts around the world. Together we’ve hosted 22 new meetups that have put us in contact with hundreds of members of our international community. Want to get involved? <a href="http://ambassadors.prestashop.com/application-form" target="_blank">Apply today</a>.</p>
<hr />
</p>
<p><img src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2016/01/look-back-2015-6-1024x537.jpg" alt="look-back-2015-6" width="700" height="367" class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-21069" /></p>
<h2 style="text-align: center; font-weight: 700">2</h2>
<p>New HQ’s. Both our teams made a move this year. Our <a href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/guided-visit-prestashops-new-paris-headquarters/">Paris</a> team moved into the city while the <a href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/discover-new-miami-hq/">Miami crew</a> headed down the block. Check out how we’ve redesigned our new offices.</p>
<hr />
</p>
<p>Want to <a href="https://www.prestashop.com/en/careers">join our team</a>? Check out our openings online or email us your cover letter and resume at <a href="mailto:hr@prestashop.com">hr@prestashop.com</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/look-back-2015/">A look back at 2015</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en">EN - Ecommerce blog by PrestaShop</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/look-back-2015/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>E-commerce Calendar: 60 secrets for a successful 2016</title>
		<link>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/e-commerce-calendar-60-secrets-successful-2016/</link>
		<comments>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/e-commerce-calendar-60-secrets-successful-2016/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 15:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Cécile Dubouis]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce Tips and Advice]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/?p=21044</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>You’ve been waiting for it… your 2016 e-commerce calendar is here! You’ll find everything you need to make 2016 another great year, including suggestions for preparing successful promotions in your online store, key sales events in your country, ideas and tips for boosting traffic and conversion rates, improving user experience, increasing average cart value, retaining [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/e-commerce-calendar-60-secrets-successful-2016/">E-commerce Calendar: 60 secrets for a successful 2016</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en">EN - Ecommerce blog by PrestaShop</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You’ve been waiting for it… your <a href="https://www.prestashop.com/en/ecommerce-calendar" title="2016 e-commerce calendar" target="_blank">2016 e-commerce calendar</a> is here!</p>
<p>You’ll find everything you need to make 2016 another great year, including suggestions for preparing successful promotions in your online store, key sales events in your country, ideas and tips for boosting traffic and conversion rates, improving user experience, increasing average cart value, retaining customers, and optimizing store management.</p>
<p>Before we go on, we’d like to give a shout out to <a href="http://www.pagination.com/" title="Pagination.com" target="_blank">Pagination.com</a> for their help integrating the template and data. Thanks!</p>
<p><span id="more-21044"></span></p>
<h2 style="color: #2E74B5;">The essential tool for all e-merchants</h2>
<p>Here at PrestaShop, our mission is to help you lead a successful e-commerce project.</p>
<p>Over the course of many meetings and e-commerce site audits, we were struck by the fact that no tool existed to help e-merchants organize their work on a daily basis. This surprised us, since an e-merchant&#8217;s job feels more like 12 jobs rolled into one&#8211;difficult to plan ahead and prioritize without visibility.</p>
<p>So three years ago, we decided to create the circular calendar, which is now downloaded worldwide each year, and gives merchants a clear idea of when to start preparing for each sales promotion.</p>
<p><strong>We hope downloading the ecommerce calendar means less stress and better organization to make your sales campaigns a success!</strong></p>
<h2 style="color: #2E74B5;">A global success</h2>
<p><strong>Wherever you are, take advantage of these tips!</strong></p>
<p>Our e-commerce calendar is available in 7 languages and customized for 8 countries (France, Germany, Italy, the Netherlands, Poland, Spain, the United Kingdom and the United States).<br />
In 2015, our e-commerce calendar was downloaded across the world and featured on ecommerce hubs. We’re thrilled that it’s been able to help merchants everywhere better manage their businesses.</p>
<h2 style="color: #2E74B5;">12 pages to help you succeed all year long</h2>
<p><strong>Each week: one tip…</strong>to boost traffic or conversion rates, improve user experience, increase average cart value or retain customers, and more!</p>
<p><strong>Know when and how to prepare for each major sales event</strong> (sales, Christmas, Mother&#8217;s Day, Black Friday, etc.), but also for specific events in 2016 (The Olympic Games, Euro 2016, etc.). You now have the means to get ahead and know when and how to start preparing your e-commerce site.</p>
<p><strong>The secrets to success of other e-merchants.</strong> Every month, an e-merchant shares his or her advice with you. Take advantage of it! </p>
<p><strong>A selection of tools to make your life easier.</strong> For each tip, you will find a selection of modules that enable you to easily create and send newsletters, generate promotions in just a few clicks, optimize store management, and more.</p>
<h2 style="color: #2E74B5;">Customize your calendar</h2>
<p>These tips are just suggestions from e-commerce experts to help you enhance your online store, get organized, and see your website in a whole new light. Don’t get discouraged if you’re not doing these things yet—you’re on your way!</p>
<p>The calendar also contains sections that need filling in. By you.<br />
You know your customers, products and website culture better than anyone else. Make a note right now of the campaigns you wish to put in place and start planning for them in advance.<br />
<strong>Remember, your store is unique. </strong></p>
<p>Wishing you all a fantastic 2016 and a successful e-commerce year!</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a style="font-size: 30px;" href="https://www.prestashop.com/en/ecommerce-calendar" target="_blank" title="e-commerce calendar 2016"><strong>Download my calendar now</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/e-commerce-calendar-60-secrets-successful-2016/">E-commerce Calendar: 60 secrets for a successful 2016</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en">EN - Ecommerce blog by PrestaShop</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/e-commerce-calendar-60-secrets-successful-2016/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>7 Things to Try in 2016</title>
		<link>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/7-things-try-2016/</link>
		<comments>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/7-things-try-2016/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 13:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kate Robinson]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce Tips and Advice]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/?p=21011</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Instead of making the same irrealistic New Year’s resolutions as you did last year, why not focus on making a few lasting changes to strengthen your online business? The secret is setting out clear, specific goals that you can easily tackle and measure. Here are a few ideas for 2016. 1. Start a newsletter. If [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/7-things-try-2016/">7 Things to Try in 2016</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en">EN - Ecommerce blog by PrestaShop</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Instead of making the same irrealistic New Year’s resolutions as you did last year, why not focus on making a few lasting changes to strengthen your online business? The secret is setting out clear, specific goals that you can easily tackle and measure. Here are a few ideas for 2016.</p>
<p><span id="more-21011"></span></p>
<h2 style="color: #39369d">1. Start a newsletter.</h2>
<p>If you haven’t started an email newsletter yet, now is a good time. Newsletters are a great way to keep your customers in the loop about your company’s latest news, build loyalty, and increase traffic. Be sure to send your newsletter regularly so your customers don’t forget about you. Regularly might mean every month, every two weeks or even every week, just make sure it’s consistent. <a href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/send_newsletters_to_your_clients/">Keep your topics short and sweet, and put time into creating quality content</a>.</p>
<p>Still not sure? Check this out: a 2013 study by the Direct Marketing Association found that 66% of shoppers have made a purchase online as a direct result of an email marketing message. That’s worth remembering.</p>
<h2 style="color: #39369d">2. Commit to updating your blog more often.</h2>
<p>This is an easy one (it should be anyway!). Sit down with a calendar and map out posts for the next three months. Commit to writing posts ahead of time and scheduling them for automatic publication.</p>
<h2 style="color: #39369d">3. Reach out to partners.</h2>
<p>To expand your reach, think about partnering up with other businesses. Could you run a marketing campaign with another local business? Or what about teaming up with another company to order supplies in bulk and benefit from lower prices? Maybe you could develop a branded product with another company? Whatever you decide, make sure to choose businesses that share your values and target the same customer base.</p>
<h2 style="color: #39369d">4. Implement monthly A/B testing.</h2>
<p>If you’ve never done <a href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/can-start-using-ab-testing-site-low-traffic/">A/B testing</a>, start this year. But don’t do too much at once; choose an element to test each month and use your findings to improve your site. Adding data to your toolkit will allow you to get a feel for what really works and make business judgements based on fact, not gut feeling.</p>
<h2 style="color: #39369d">5. Schedule 10 minutes of daily market research.</h2>
<p>Running a business is time consuming as it is, but don’t overlook staying informed. Take time each morning to find out what’s going on in your industry. What are your competitors doing? What are your customers saying in forums? What’s happening in industries similar to yours? This kind of daily research will help you decide what business decisions to take and what elements to test and adjust, and it will also provide inspiration to keep your business fresh and relevant.</p>
<h2 style="color: #39369d">6. Contact the press.</h2>
<p>Social media gets a lot of attention these days, but have you thought about contacting the old fashioned press? Starting with your local newspaper, commit to contacting two press outlets a month. Reach out to bloggers, pitch online versions of print publications and get in touch with your local radio station. Set a goal of 5 to 10 press features for this year and see how they impact your business.</p>
<h2 style="color: #39369d">7. Find a mentor.</h2>
<p>No matter where you’re at in your business journey, it’s always helpful to get some outside advice. Consider asking someone you admire to mentor you. Decide what qualities you’d like to cultivate and what long term goals you’d like to achieve, and then approach the person with a plan. Mentoring could be as simple as sharing thoughts over coffee once a week or as involved as assessing your 5-year business plan. Decide what’s right for your business and go for it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/7-things-try-2016/">7 Things to Try in 2016</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en">EN - Ecommerce blog by PrestaShop</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/7-things-try-2016/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Discover our new Miami HQ</title>
		<link>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/discover-new-miami-hq/</link>
		<comments>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/discover-new-miami-hq/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 13:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Julie Liu]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[PrestaShop News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/?p=20997</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Following the relocation of our Paris HQ earlier this year, the Miami HQ had to follow suit, of course! Earlier this month we moved down the street from our old office into a new, redesigned and Preston-inspired office. Check out our new Miami nest! Welcome to our new Miami Office! We had to bring our [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/discover-new-miami-hq/">Discover our new Miami HQ</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en">EN - Ecommerce blog by PrestaShop</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Following the relocation of our Paris HQ earlier this year, the Miami HQ had to follow suit, of course! Earlier this month we moved down the street from our old office into a new, redesigned and Preston-inspired office. Check out our new Miami nest!<br />
<span id="more-20997"></span><br />
Welcome to our new Miami Office!</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-21002" alt="MiamiHQ1" src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2015/12/MiamiHQ1-1024x575.jpg" width="700" height="393" /></p>
<p>We had to bring our foosball table, which we’ve proudly displayed in our lobby &#8212; and we’re always ready for a challenge.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-21003" alt="MiamiHQ2" src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2015/12/MiamiHQ2-1024x575.jpg" width="700" height="393" /></p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-21004" alt="MiamiHQ3" src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2015/12/MiamiHQ3-1024x768.jpg" width="700" height="525" /></p>
<p>We brought some street art indoors, with our custom PrestaShop graffiti. Although we’ve moved locations, our merchant success team is still here to provide you all the help and guidance you need to succeed.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-20998" alt="MiamiHQ5" src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2015/12/MiamiHQ5-1024x575.jpg" width="700" height="393" /></p>
<p>Sometimes we need to chill out after during a long day. Here’s where we relax and reboot, or meet with our team to come up with more great ideas.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-20999" alt="MiamiHQ6" src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2015/12/MiamiHQ6-1024x575.jpg" width="700" height="393" /></p>
<p>One of our many new offices with a view overlooking Miami.</p>
<div class="row">
<div class="col-sm-6"><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-21000" alt="MiamiHQ7" src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2015/12/MiamiHQ7-986x1024.jpg" width="700" height="726" /></div>
<div class="col-sm-6"><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-21001" alt="MiamiHQ8" src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2015/12/MiamiHQ8-1007x1024.jpg" width="700" height="711" /></div>
</div>
<p>Who says one mascot is ever enough? Meet Julius, our jumping Beta Fish and Levy, our rescue Chihuahua pup.</p>
<p>Want to join the team in our Miami office? Check out our Careers page and send us your application today! Want to see more? Head on over to Pinterest and take a look at our Working at PrestaShop board or follow us on Instagram @prestacrew.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/discover-new-miami-hq/">Discover our new Miami HQ</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en">EN - Ecommerce blog by PrestaShop</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/discover-new-miami-hq/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>4</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>12 tips to stay healthy during the holidays</title>
		<link>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/12-tips-stay-healthy-holidays/</link>
		<comments>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/12-tips-stay-healthy-holidays/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 13:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kate Robinson]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce Tips and Advice]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/?p=20982</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The holidays are a busy time of year for everyone, but e-store owners have the added challenge of managing a thriving business in the midst of holiday madness. The extra pressure can build up fast and take its toll. No one needs to get sick or have a nervous breakdown a week before Christmas. Here [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/12-tips-stay-healthy-holidays/">12 tips to stay healthy during the holidays</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en">EN - Ecommerce blog by PrestaShop</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The holidays are a busy time of year for everyone, but e-store owners have the added challenge of managing a thriving business in the midst of holiday madness. The extra pressure can build up fast and take its toll. No one needs to get sick or have a nervous breakdown a week before Christmas. Here are a few simple ways to take care of yourself during the holidays.<br />
<span id="more-20982"></span><br />
<em>On the first day of Christmas&#8230;Schedule your time.</em><br />
It’s tempting to devote your days and nights to your business at the holidays&#8211;this is the most important time of the year after all, right? But you won’t be efficient glued to your screen 16 hours a day. Plan chunks of time to get specific tasks done, and plan time to spend with family, friends, or just relaxing. You need a balance to be productive.</p>
<p><em>On the second day of Christmas&#8230;Plan workouts.</em><br />
Whether it’s shoveling snow or going for a jog, you need to keep moving! Exercise keeps your mood up and the eggnog calories off.</p>
<p><em>On the third day of Christmas&#8230;Get up and move around.</em><br />
It’s just as important to get up and take regular breaks while you’re working as it is to schedule exercise. Flex those knees and stretch out those wrists!</p>
<p><em>On the fourth day of Christmas&#8230;Eat healthy. </em><br />
It’s difficult this time of year, but try to resist overindulging in holiday treats. Keep healthy snacks like veggie sticks and low-fat yoghurt around if you plan on putting in a few extra hours. Save the desserts for meal times and special moments.</p>
<p><em>On the fifth day of Christmas…Put your computer away.</em><br />
Yes, you are allowed to unplug during the holidays. Set aside blocks of time to shut down your computer and forget about work. When you log back on, you’ll be refreshed and focused. Setting boundaries in this way will make you more efficient at work and more present during social time.</p>
<p><em>On the sixth day of Christmas…Drink water.</em><br />
Sorry if we sound like your mother, but yes, you do need to drink 8 glasses or about 1.5 liters of water a day to stay healthy and alert. This is even more important if your December tends to be awash in bubbly.</p>
<p><em>On the seventh day of Christmas…Communicate.</em><br />
Stay in touch with your customers and communicate early if you see weather or supply-related delays on the horizon. Being proactive will protect you from customer ire and make managing the post-holiday exchange and return period less stressful.</p>
<p><em>On the eighth day of Christmas…Prioritize</em><br />
Not everything is going to make or break your holiday performance, so prioritize and get the essentials done first. Then, if you have the time and motivation, do a few less important tasks. But stay realistic, or you’ll miss out on what the holidays are really about: friends, family and sugar cookies, lots of sugar cookies.</p>
<p><em>On the ninth day of Christmas…Meditate.</em><br />
Take some time for yourself, even if it’s just ten or twenty minutes in the morning or at the end of the day. Settle down in a quiet spot and focus on your breath to quiet your mind and let go of whatever stress is currently weighing you down. Meditation won’t make your problems go away, but you’ll be better prepared to tackle them after a moment of calm and self-care.</p>
<p><em>On the tenth day of Christmas…Get up early.</em><br />
The early bird gets the worm&#8230;and she gets to enjoy the rest of the day with a clear conscience. If you can get up at 5 or 6 o’clock in the morning, you’ll have two or three hours of calm before the rest of the world gets going. If you concentrate on getting a maximum of work done then, you’ll have more than enough time for a nap in front of the fireplace later on.</p>
<p><em>On the eleventh day of Christmas…Volunteer.</em><br />
Volunteering is not everyone’s cup of tea, but it can be a great opportunity to step back and see the big picture. Your business is important, but it’s just one aspect of your life. You’re part of a community that keeps your business alive and giving back feels great. Volunteering is also an opportunity to spend meaningful time with friends and family, which will also help keep your stress in check.</p>
<p><em>On the twelfth day of Christmas&#8230;Say no.</em><br />
Sometimes the best thing to do is simply to not do. It’s okay if you can’t get it all done. You’re better off saying no to an invitation or rescheduling a non-vital task to tomorrow if trying to fit everything in is going to leave you frazzled. The holidays are important because they generate a lot of revenue, but don’t let that become such an obsession that it ruins the rest of the experience.</p>
<p>What do you do to stay sane at the holidays? Let us know in the comments below!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/12-tips-stay-healthy-holidays/">12 tips to stay healthy during the holidays</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en">EN - Ecommerce blog by PrestaShop</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/12-tips-stay-healthy-holidays/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>3 Remedies for the Post-Holiday Ecommerce Sales Slump</title>
		<link>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/3-remedies-post-holiday-ecommerce-sales-slump/</link>
		<comments>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/3-remedies-post-holiday-ecommerce-sales-slump/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 09:33:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kate Robinson]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce Tips and Advice]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/?p=19408</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The holidays are over&#8211;phew! But that doesn’t mean your work is! Smart ecommerce business owners will take this opportunity to rocket into 2016 with the same energy that got them record sales in 2015. The truth is, though, many merchants check out after Christmas, resulting in the dreaded post-holiday slump. Don’t let that happen to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/3-remedies-post-holiday-ecommerce-sales-slump/">3 Remedies for the Post-Holiday Ecommerce Sales Slump</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en">EN - Ecommerce blog by PrestaShop</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">The holidays are over&#8211;phew! But that doesn’t mean your work is! Smart ecommerce business owners will take this opportunity to rocket into 2016 with the same energy that got them record sales in 2015. The truth is, though, many merchants check out after Christmas, resulting in the dreaded post-holiday slump. Don’t let that happen to you. Read on to discover our suggestions for extending the holiday cheer all the way into the new year.</p>
<p><span id="more-19408"></span></p>
<p>Here are a few alternative ideas to ensure healthy business after the holiday rush, and cultivate good relationships with new and existing customers.</p>
<h2 style="color: #5e8f71;">Returns and exchanges</h2>
<p>Your customers are burnt out from the holidays and dreading the entire return-and-exchange process. If you can make the experience easy, or better yet, pleasant for them, you can turn this dreary aspect of the holidays into an opportunity to build customer loyalty.</p>
<p><strong>Unsatisfied customers are people too</strong><br />
You worked hard to deck out your online shop for the holidays and make sure your customers had a stellar experience. Don&#8217;t stop now; returns and exchanges may not be fun, but they provide a great opportunity to impress your customers with attentive, personalized service.</p>
<p><strong>Lend a listening ear with instant chat</strong><br />
The best way to ease the returns and exchange process is to have a simple policy clearly stated on your shop site. Back this up with enhanced <span style="text-decoration: underline;">live chat</span> capabilities—this is your chance to show off your customer service skills with friendly, real-time help. As an added bonus, personalize your live chat windows with photos of real people, not stock shots.</p>
<p><strong>Reduce returns with an incentive they can&#8217;t refuse</strong><br />
Looked at in another light, a return can be a great opportunity to convert a long-term customer. Why not offer free shipping or a modest discount if the customer decides to make an exchange instead of asking for a refund? They get a pleasant surprise and you get renewed business.</p>
<h2 style="color: #5e8f71;">Deals and discounts that make a difference</h2>
<p>We wouldn&#8217;t usually tell you to compete on price, but the holiday and post-holiday period is a unique time when customers expect discounts. That doesn&#8217;t mean you have to do what everyone else is doing; find a unique way to stand out as customers get ready to spend their Christmas loot and cash in on gift cards. Try one of these:</p>
<p><strong>Give back a bit of what you get</strong><br />
An interesting way to differentiate yourself is to give a portion of proceeds to a charity you support. After months in the consumerist tornado that is the holiday season, many people are happy to see some of their money support a good cause.</p>
<p><strong>Buy one, get this free</strong><br />
If you’ve got excess inventory to move, consider offering a free product with the purchase of a full-price item. This works very well with perishable or time-sensitive products, like seasonal fashion items: throw in a printed scarf for every pair of full-price jeans purchased. Even if you only break even on those items, you’ve saved yourself invenotry costs and shelf space by moving products that would have otherwise gone to waste.</p>
<p><strong>Bundle up</strong><br />
If you have complimentary products that you need to get rid of, consider bundling them and targeting customers who bought a related item. Accessories and refills are great candidates for this move: picks and strings for a new guitar; chargers, adapters and cases for phones. Mix and match to see what works for your business.</p>
<p><strong>A good old-fashioned contest</strong><br />
Drum up interest with a contest: ask customers to submit their favorite holiday photos or best image of your product in use. Everyone who participates wins, even if it’s just 5% off their next purchase. Use the contest to promote a new or best-selling product and award one to the winner.</p>
<p><strong>Say thank you</strong><br />
Your store’s success leans heavily on customer loyalty, so why not thank your customers for making your year a great one? Offer them a small discount that they can pass on to friends and family. It’ll give them a reason to visit your store in January and maybe even attract a few new visitors.</p>
<p><strong>The undiscount: a new product for the new year</strong><br />
A new product launch is a great way to get customers’ attention without slashing prices. You’ll need to be organized to pull it off, but if you do it right, you can take advantage of new year momentum to make a big impact.</p>
<h2 style="color: #5e8f71;">Lessons and resolutions</h2>
<p>The post-holiday season is also a good time to take stock of the past year in order to prepare for the one coming up. While you’ll certainly be discounting some items and working to clear inventory for new products, it’s important to take the time to do important marketing work that will put you on track for the NEXT holiday season.</p>
<p><strong>Mind your data</strong><br />
The holiday season should have given you a wealth of data about your customers. You can use it to segment your contact list and push personalized offers on products you want to move to the customers you’re sure will be interested. For example, if you know who bought a phone this year, send an email offering an accessory bundle. Or if you’re an apparel store with excess items in a few select sizes, send targeted offers to customers you know have bought those sizes previously. You avoid swamping customers with offers that won’t interest them.</p>
<p><strong>Pay attention to purchasing patterns</strong><br />
You’ll have learned a lot about your customers this holiday season, but also quite a bit about your products. What is selling full price? What goes on sale? Use this data to tailor your marketing and evaluate which products you should be marking down to move and which are going to carry you through the year.</p>
<ul style="margin-left: 30px;">
<li><strong style="color: #5e8f71;">Well-performing products:</strong> The holidays probably gave you a good idea of what products people are willing to pay full price for. These are good items to build bundles and promotions around now and to focus marketing efforts on throughout the year.</li>
<li><strong style="color: #5e8f71;">Products with promise:</strong> Do some products attract a lot of attention but few conversions? Try promoting them with a light post-holiday sale or simply put them in the spotlight when you communicate with customers.</li>
<li><strong style="color: #5e8f71;">Troubled products:</strong> if certain products only sell well at a discount it might be time to clear them out. Post-holiday sales are a great opportunity to make a special “Clearance” category. These are products that might also bundle well.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Don’t neglect abandoned carts</strong><br />
Many customers use carts in lieu of a wish list. They often expect to receive a reminder about their cart, so don’t miss this opportunity to follow up and recoup unfinished sales.</p>
<p><strong>Show off your social skills </strong><br />
The holidays may be over, but don’t shelve your marketing efforts just yet. Use social media to keep the conversation going. If you decide to incorporate a charity donation, social media is a great way to engage your customers and raise awareness. The same goes for if you hold a post-holiday contest.</p>
<p><strong>Take down the holiday decorations (and deals!)</strong><br />
This is one that’s easy to do, but also easy to overlook. Unfortunately, the consequences of forgetting could be unpleasant for your reputation and your bottom line. If you promised free shipping during the holidays, be sure to remove it from your promotional tools if you don’t plan on continuing in the new year. Did you make a low-price guarantee during the holidays that your post-holiday sale is going to conflict with? Do this now so you can move on to more important things.</p>
<h2 style="color: #5e8f71;">Key takeaways</h2>
<ul style="margin-left: 30px;">
<li>Personalize the returns and exchange process</li>
<li>Use incentives to convert returns into exchanges or even purchases</li>
<li>Avoid relying solely on deep discounts; make creative offers</li>
<li>Thank your customers</li>
<li>Use data to segment customers and target marketing efforts</li>
<li>Analyze product performance and market accordingly</li>
<li>Follow up on abandoned cards</li>
<li>Be social in the new year</li>
<li>Review holiday promises and take down decorations</li>
</ul>
<p>The holidays are over, but the new year is just beginning. What are you doing to make sure it’s a successful one? Have you tried any of these suggestions? Let us know what’s working for you!</p>
<hr align="left" size="2" width="20%" />
<p>Ready to make 2016 your best year yet? Get started with our updated 2016 <a href="http://www.prestashop.com/en/ecommerce-calendar">ecommerce calendar</a>. From expert advice to key sales dates, it has everything you need to prepare your year.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/3-remedies-post-holiday-ecommerce-sales-slump/">3 Remedies for the Post-Holiday Ecommerce Sales Slump</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en">EN - Ecommerce blog by PrestaShop</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/3-remedies-post-holiday-ecommerce-sales-slump/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Boast a new status in 2016: Become a PrestaShop Ambassador!</title>
		<link>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/boast-new-status-2016-become-prestashop-ambassador/</link>
		<comments>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/boast-new-status-2016-become-prestashop-ambassador/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 09:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sabrina Maréchal]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[PrestaShop Ambassadors]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/?p=20964</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Open-source and PrestaShop lover? You can become the next PrestaShop Ambassador in your city. Keep reading to discover how you could be part of this great adventure! What is a PrestaShop Ambassador? A PrestaShop Ambassador is a trusted PrestaShop Community member who has volunteered to be PrestaShop&#8217;s voice in his region. Merchants, developers, designers or [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/boast-new-status-2016-become-prestashop-ambassador/">Boast a new status in 2016: Become a PrestaShop Ambassador!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en">EN - Ecommerce blog by PrestaShop</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Open-source and PrestaShop lover? You can become the next PrestaShop Ambassador in your city. Keep reading to discover how you could be part of this great adventure!<br />
<span id="more-20964"></span></p>
<h2 style="color:#df0067">What is a PrestaShop Ambassador?</h2>
<p>A PrestaShop Ambassador is a trusted PrestaShop Community member who has volunteered to be PrestaShop&#8217;s voice in his region.</p>
<p>Merchants, developers, designers or consultants, PrestaShop Ambassadors are all ecommerce rock stars who love sharing their knowledge with their local community to make great things happen.</p>
<p>They initiate a wide variety of community-building activities and receive cool perks.</p>
<p><em>&gt; PrestaShop Ambassadors are individuals. If you are a web agency interested in getting more involved in the PrestaShop Community, <a href="https://www.prestashop.com/en/certification-details" target="_blank">learn more about our agency program</a>.</em></p>
<h2 style="color:#df0067">Which activities can an Ambassador initiate?</h2>
<p>Online, offline, product oriented or just fun and social activities &#8211; the sky is the limit. Here’s a look at what other Ambassadors have done in the past:</p>
<ul style="padding-left: 30px">
<li>Inspire conversation and moderate their local Forum on www.prestashop.com</li>
<li>Actively participate in discussions about PrestaShop on social networks, StackOverflow, Quora, etc.</li>
<li>Run local tests on upcoming releases, provide local input on the software and its features</li>
<li>Participate in PrestaShop&#8217;s translations or documentation on <a href="https://crowdin.com/project/prestashop-official" target="_blank">Crowdin</a></li>
<li>Organize Community MeetUps, Webinars or Google Hangouts On Air</li>
<li>Create videos or written tutorials about using or coding with PrestaShop</li>
<li>Write guest blog posts on local topics for <a href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/" target="_blank">the official PrestaShop blog</a></li>
<li>Get in touch with local influencers</li>
<li>&#8230; And more! We’re always open to new ideas.</li>
</ul>
<h2 style="color:#df0067">Which perks do Ambassadors receive?</h2>
<p>Besides local expert visibility, PrestaShop Ambassador benefit from:</p>
<p><strong>1) Online Recognition</strong><br />
<em>We’ll provide you with your own PrestaShop Ambassador badge, set you up with a profile on <a href="http://ambassadors.prestashop.com/ambassadors" target="_blank">our website</a>, and even make you a moderator on our forum. Best of all, we’ll feature your events on our website, blog and social media to bring more visibility and awareness to the awesome things you are doing.</em></p>
<p><strong>2) Free Training</strong><br />
<em>Regardless of your technical level, we have a training course that suits you. User, Developer and Integrator training sessions are free for our Ambassadors – so take a refresher course or learn some new skills!</em></p>
<p><strong>3) Goodies, of course</strong><br />
<em>We’re sending Preston to you, a plushy that is, along with an Ambassador Kit complete with goodies that will make all your office mates jealous.</em></p>
<p><strong>4) Exclusive access </strong><br />
<em>Being a PrestaShop Ambassador means getting insider information on our latest developments. You’ll know some PrestaShop news before they’re officially announced. You’ll even get to participate in regular Q&amp;A sessions with the product team.</em></p>
<p><strong>5) PrestaShop Support </strong><br />
<em>The best part about being a PrestaShop Ambassador is the support you’ll receive from the PrestaShop team. If you’re already hosting a webinar, we’ll help increase the number of attendees by promoting the event. Inviting people out for a local Meetup? We’ll send goodies for the current and future PrestaShop fans!</em></p>
<p><strong>6) Many, many more! </strong><br />
<em>There are so many perks of being a PrestaShop Ambassador, check out <a href="http://ambassadors.prestashop.com/" target="_blank">our page</a> or chat with our current Ambassadors to see what you’re missing out.</em></p>
<h2 style="color:#df0067">What is it like, exactly?</h2>
<p>As of today, we have <a href="http://ambassadors.prestashop.com/ambassadors" target="_blank">24 devoted Ambassadors</a> across 15 countries.<br />
Here are some examples of their latest achievements:</p>
<ul style="padding-left: 30px">
<li>Community Meetups: most of PrestaShop Ambassadors hold regular meetups in their city – it’s great <a href="http://ambassadors.prestashop.com/galleries" target="_blank">seeing so many communities gathering</a> to share ecommerce knowledge all across the world, from Lima to Düsseldorf, passing by Rio de Janeiro and Dakar <img src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif" alt=":)" class="wp-smiley" /> </li>
<li>Translations: like <a href="http://ambassadors.prestashop.com/ambassador/michael-dekker" target="_blank">Michael</a> who translated the whole <a href="http://doc.prestashop.com/display/PS16/Nederlandse+documentatie" target="_blank">user documentation in Dutch</a>, or <a href="http://ambassadors.prestashop.com/ambassador/deyson-thom%C3%A9" target="_blank">Thomé</a> who translates modules for the Brazilian market.</li>
<li>GitHub contributions: like <a href="http://ambassadors.prestashop.com/ambassador/jonathan-danse" target="_blank">Jonathan</a> who counts over 200 pull requests!</li>
<li>Blog posts: like <a href="http://ambassadors.prestashop.com/ambassador/nicolas-creanico" target="_blank">Nicolas</a> who <a href="http://www.creanico.fr/prestashop/dans-les-coulisses-de-prestashop/" target="_blank">visited our team in Paris</a> and introduced <a href="http://www.creanico.fr/prestashop/nouveautes-de-prestashop-1-7/" target="_blank">a sneak peek of the next version of the software</a></li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2015/12/photos-meetups.png"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-20976" alt="photos-meetups" src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2015/12/photos-meetups.png" width="657" height="345" /></a></p>
<h2 style="color:#df0067">Want to apply?</h2>
<p><strong>We’ve opened 20 new spots today. If you are a true PrestaShop lover volunteering to share your experience and educate your local community about PrestaShop and ecommerce in general, <a href="http://ambassadors.prestashop.com/application-form" target="_blank">apply today</a>!</strong></p>
<p>We’re currently looking for people in the following cities / regions. If you’re not in the region but would like to apply anyway, we, of course, encourage you to do so!</p>
<p><strong>Europe:</strong></p>
<ul style="padding-left: 30px">
<li>Amsterdam, Netherlands</li>
<li>Brussels, Belgium</li>
<li>Berlin, Germany</li>
<li>Helsinki, Finland</li>
<li>Lisbon, Portugal</li>
<li>London, England</li>
<li>Manchester, England</li>
<li>Munich, Germany</li>
<li>Prague, Czech Republic</li>
<li>Vienna, Austria</li>
<li>Vilnius, Lithuania</li>
<li>Zurich, Switzerland</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>USA:</strong></p>
<ul style="padding-left: 30px">
<li>Los Angeles, CA</li>
<li>New York City, NY</li>
<li>Seattle, WA</li>
<li>Silicon Valley, between San Francisco and San Jose</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Central and South Americas:</strong></p>
<ul style="padding-left: 30px">
<li>Mexico City, Mexico</li>
<li>Santiago, Chile</li>
</ul>
<p><strong><a href="http://ambassadors.prestashop.com/application-form" target="_blank">Grab your spot by applying today!</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/boast-new-status-2016-become-prestashop-ambassador/">Boast a new status in 2016: Become a PrestaShop Ambassador!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en">EN - Ecommerce blog by PrestaShop</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/boast-new-status-2016-become-prestashop-ambassador/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>It&#8217;s the Anti-Spam Time of the Season</title>
		<link>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/anti-spam-time-season/</link>
		<comments>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/anti-spam-time-season/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 13:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Preston's Friends]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce Tips and Advice]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/?p=20950</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Today Leah Hamilton from Terms Feed gives us the low-down on how to avoid spamming customers during the holiday season. At holiday time, when you’re sending out mailers, special deals, and seasonal sales, the name of the game is to market your product, and market hard. The winter holidays are the biggest spending season of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/anti-spam-time-season/">It&#8217;s the Anti-Spam Time of the Season</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en">EN - Ecommerce blog by PrestaShop</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Today Leah Hamilton from Terms Feed gives us the low-down on how to avoid spamming customers during the holiday season.</em></p>
<p>At holiday time, when you’re sending out mailers, special deals, and seasonal sales, the name of the game is to market your product, and market hard. The winter holidays are the biggest spending season of the year, and it’s highly likely that <a href="http://www.marketingcharts.com/online/marketers-continue-to-rate-email-the-most-effective-digital-marketing-tactic-46295/" target="_blank">email marketing </a>will be one of your primary methods of reaching your customers. Given the crucial importance of marketing at this time, it’s important to remember to comply with anti-spam legislation when you carry out your marketing plan.</p>
<p>First we’ll take a look at why Christmas and holiday-season marketing is so important for your business, then look at how to make sure you get it right, legally.<br />
<span id="more-20950"></span></p>
<h2 style="color: #5c69af">Marketing in the Holiday Season</h2>
<p>The winter holiday season is definitely the most lucrative of the year; and it’s not just Christmas, either: more than 90 percent of Americans celebrated Christmas, Kwanza or Hanukah in 2014, and spent an <a href="http://research.nrffoundation.com/Default.aspx?pg=9003#.U2E-1_ldVyw" target="_blank">average of $730</a> on gifts, food, and decorations. Check out the graph from the National Retail Federation that shows just how far ahead the winter holidays are:</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-20952" alt="holiday-spending-totals" src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2015/12/holiday-spending-totals.png" width="674" height="573" /></p>
<p><em style="font-size: 13px">Image: NRF Consumer Holiday Spending USA (<a href="https://nrf.com/news/the-long-and-short-of-americas-consumer-holidays" target="_blank">https://nrf.com/news/the-long-and-short-of-americas-consumer-holidays</a>)</em></p>
<p>It’s easy to see why merchants ramp up their marketing efforts this time of year: everyone is on the lookout for gifts for friends and family, special deals and themed products. Marketers need to capitalize on this opportunity by sending out their latest specials, catalogues and holiday-themed emails. Given the importance of the holiday season to many people, getting it right means an opportunity to build customer loyalty and a chance to capitalize on goodwill.</p>
<p>However, it’s important to make sure that holiday marketing is done right. Here’s where CAN-SPAM and other pieces of anti-spam law come in. First let’s take a look at the anti-spam legislation in the US, as well as the UK and Europe, and then we’ll look at some holiday examples of how to comply.</p>
<h2 style="color: #5c69af">What Are the Key Pieces of Anti-Spam Legislation?</h2>
<h4>Anti-Spam in Europe and the UK</h4>
<p>In Europe, anti-spam rules are covered by the <a href="http://www.email-marketing-reports.com/canspam/eu/" target="_blank">Privacy and Electronic Communication Directive</a>, issued in 2002. EU Member States are expected to implement this Directive in their own local laws. The UK has done this by way of the <a href="https://ico.org.uk/for-the-public/online/spam-emails/" target="_blank">Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003</a>, which sets out a number of rules that must be followed when sending out marketing emails.</p>
<p>First, to email or market to someone who isn’t already a customer, you must offer them a chance to <a href="https://termsfeed.com/blog/legal-mistakes-uk-email-marketing/" target="_blank">opt in explicitly</a>. Here’s an example of what an explicit opt-in looks like:</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-20953" alt="join-our-mailing-list" src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2015/12/join-our-mailing-list.png" width="880" height="603" /></p>
<p><em>Image: <a href="https://www.katespade.com/katespade-customer-service-your-account/join-mailing-list.html" target="_blank">Kate Spade Mailing List</a></em></p>
<p>You can see in the image above that Kate Spade asks for an email address and for the user to click a “Join” button before product announcements, promotions or sales reminders are sent to the customer. They also include a link to their privacy policy and terms of use, which is good practice.</p>
<p>UK anti-spam law also allows something called a <a href="http://www.lawdonut.co.uk/law/sales-and-marketing/marketing-and-advertising/your-email-marketing-and-anti-spam-law" target="_blank">soft opt-in</a>. This soft opt-in allows you to treat a customer as if they have consented to receiving emails from you, even though they actually haven’t. To comply with the soft opt-in allowance you need to:</p>
<ul style="padding-left: 30px">
<li>Have <strong>obtained the customer’s email address “in the course of the sale of negotiations for the sale of a product or service.”</strong> This means that the person has to be already a customer, and you can’t just email random people.</li>
<li><strong>Only email those people in relation to “similar products and services.”</strong> So if your customers signed up to receive jewellery newsletters from you, you can’t send them advertisements for gardening supplies.</li>
<li><strong>Give the person a method of refusing the use of his or her contact details</strong> at the time they initially provide them.</li>
</ul>
<p>Like US law (which we’ll discuss below) UK law also requires that you give your customers an opportunity to opt-out of emails that you send them. The option to unsubscribe must be <strong>easily visible, and displayed on every email</strong>.</p>
<h4>CAN-SPAM and the US</h4>
<p>In the US, the primary governing law is CAN-SPAM. CAN-SPAM stands for <a href="https://www.ftc.gov/tips-advice/business-center/guidance/can-spam-act-compliance-guide-business" target="_blank">Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography And Marketing Act of 2003</a>, and it is a piece of legislation that sets the rules for commercial emails, such as holiday advertisements.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.ftc.gov/tips-advice/business-center/guidance/can-spam-act-compliance-guide-business" target="_blank">main requirements of CAN-SPAM</a> are:</p>
<ul style="padding-left: 30px">
<li>Don’t use misleading header information in your emails. For instance, don’t change your “From” text to say that your name is “National Hospital” when it (clearly) isn’t. Your email address and domain name should be accurate.</li>
<li>Don’t use deceptive subject lines. Don’t use “Fwd:” or “Re:” in your email header just to make it look more like your recipient has already contacted you. Or alternatively, if your email is a marketing email about your product, don’t make your subject line “URGENT: Mom ill!” Your subject line should accurately reflect the contact of your email.</li>
<li>If you are sending marketing messages, you must identify your message as an advertisement in some way.</li>
<li>You must notify your recipients of where you are located. In particular, you must provide a valid physical postal address (e.g. street address, PO box, private mailbox).</li>
<li>Include opt-out information for your recipients.</li>
<li>Honor any opt-out requests. You must do this within 10 business days, and there must not be a fee for your recipient to opt out.</li>
<li>If someone else is sending marketing emails on your behalf, you must monitor what they are doing and ensure that they comply with the law.</li>
</ul>
<p>This law is enforced by the Federal Trade Commission (<strong>FTC</strong>), and if a person or organisation does not comply, they may be subject to <a href="https://sendgrid.com/blog/can-spam-compliance-breaking/" target="_blank">penalties of up to ,000</a> for each email in violation. Both the company whose product is promoted in the message, and the company who sent the message may be legally responsible.</p>
<h2 style="color: #5c69af">How to comply</h2>
<p>Let’s take a look at some examples of Christmas mailers that comply with the laws above.</p>
<p>Here’s an example from <a href="http://www.pumpkinpatch.co.nz/" target="_blank">Pumpkin Patch</a> kidswear that shows the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email:</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-20951" alt="pumpkin-patch" src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2015/12/pumpkin-patch.png" width="525" height="507" /></p>
<p>You can see that Pumpkin Patch has a link to what is essentially a preferences page, where the email recipient can change their account preferences and unsubscribe from email advertisements. It’s ok to either provide a direct unsubscribe link, or send your customers to their preferences page to do so, as Pumpkin Patch has done.</p>
<p>Next let’s take a look at an example from <a href="http://www.bhcosmetics.com/" target="_blank">BH Cosmetics</a>. In the example below you can see that BH Cosmetics has included their physical address to notify recipients of their location.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-20954" alt="last-day-to-ship" src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2015/12/last-day-to-ship.png" width="722" height="446" /></p>
<p>Finally, the last example from the <a href="https://www.portablenorthpole.com/en/" target="_blank">Portable North Pole</a> shows appropriate headers and subject lines, as well as clearly indicating that the email is an advertisement.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-20955" alt="newsletter-santa" src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2015/12/newsletter-santa-1024x719.png" width="700" height="491" /></p>
<p>You can see that the subject line, the email “from” field, and email address are all correct and honest about who the email is coming from (Portable North Pole). In the message itself, the wording “fan offer” and “get your unlimited pass and enjoy Premium video messages” clearly indicate that this is an advertisement for customers to purchase a Premium video package as opposed to the free video messages that Portable North Pole offers.</p>
<h2 style="color: #5c69af">Conclusion</h2>
<p>Advertising in the holiday season is a great way to reach your customers and get them hooked on holiday deals, but make sure to comply with anti-spam laws in your country when you email them! By including an unsubscribe link in your emails, and staying honest and truthful in all communications, you’ll be well on your way to meeting the anti-spam requirements you’ll be subject to.</p>
<p>TermsFeed allows you to create custom legal agreements online, for your ecommerce website or app. The agreements are completely free, but TermsFeed also offers premium options if you wish to use them. TermsFeed’s agreements are drafted by professional lawyers from around the world, and each agreement goes through a rigorous quality certification process. Check out their <a href="https://termsfeed.com/reviews" target="_blank">testimonials</a>! If you don’t currently have a Privacy Policy for your ecommerce store, <a href="https://termsfeed.com/" target="_blank">visit TermsFeed to create one</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/anti-spam-time-season/">It&#8217;s the Anti-Spam Time of the Season</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en">EN - Ecommerce blog by PrestaShop</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/anti-spam-time-season/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>3 tools to expand your business internationally in 2016</title>
		<link>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/3-tools-expand-business-internationally-2016/</link>
		<comments>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/3-tools-expand-business-internationally-2016/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 13:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Julie Liu]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/?p=20942</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Did you crush your holiday sales this year? With 2015 rolling to a close, it’s already time to start planning for 2016. Have you considered expanding your audience beyond your borders to reach more potential customers? We’re helping you do just that with 3 ways to expand your business internationally in 2016. 1. Set up [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/3-tools-expand-business-internationally-2016/">3 tools to expand your business internationally in 2016</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en">EN - Ecommerce blog by PrestaShop</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Did you crush your holiday sales this year? With 2015 rolling to a close, it’s already time to start planning for 2016. Have you considered expanding your audience beyond your borders to reach more potential customers? We’re helping you do just that with 3 ways to expand your business internationally in 2016.<br />
<span id="more-20942"></span></p>
<h2 style="color:#01bad9">1. Set up a multi-currency payment provider</h2>
<p>The first tool you’ll need to expand your business internationally is a payment provider that allows you to accept different currencies and process multiple payment options. Visa, MasterCard, Amex, Diners, JCB, Discover and PayPal are just a few of the popular payment options customers prefer. Next, it’s important to offer new or potential customers their preferred currency because not only are they more familiar with it, they incur fewer to no fees when they complete translations. </p>
<p><a href="http://addons.prestashop.com/en/payments-gateways-prestashop-modules/18752-brinkscheckout.html" target="_blank">Brinks Checkout</a> is one of the <a href="http://addons.prestashop.com/en/481-payment">payment methods</a> offered to PrestaShop customers. With <a href="http://addons.prestashop.com/en/payments-gateways-prestashop-modules/18752-brinkscheckout.html" target="_blank">Brinks Checkout</a>, customers can sell in almost 200 countries, accept 26 currencies and is offered in 15 languages – all with one merchant account. Consider the number of customers you can reach by adding just this tool. Check out their Addons page for more details on their offer then download their <a href="http://addons.prestashop.com/en/payments-gateways-prestashop-modules/18752-brinkscheckout.html" target="_blank">free module</a>.</p>
<p>BONUS: Use PrestaShop’s built-in localization features to translate your entire website to convert even more of your new international customer base. Simply navigate to your back office &gt; localization &gt; translations &gt; add / update a language.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-20944" alt="brinks_checkout" src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2015/12/brinks_checkout.png" width="155" height="55" /></p>
<h2 style="color:#01bad9">2. Enable international shipping options</h2>
<p>The second tool you’ll need to expand your business internationally in 2016 is a reliable and affordable way to transport your goods to the eventual customer. A few important things to consider are: shipping pricing and customs processing. You’ll need to figure out how much shipping a product overseas will cost you. Then you’ll need to decide if you want to charge your customers the entire shipping cost or if you want to offer competitive shipping prices and cover the remaining cost yourself. Keep in mind that some carriers tack on additional surcharges to deliver the package overseas.</p>
<p>Next, you should prepare the necessary information for shipping overseas. Customs declaration forms should generally accompany packages that weigh more than a pound. Depending on your carrier, you may need to detail each product, their components, weights as well as price. Be sure to have all this handy to expedite your shipping process. Once you’ve shipped to a new country, be sure to note the amount of time it takes to deliver your package.</p>
<p>Stamps.com is a shipping option that can help expand your international shipping options and promote your shop’s growth. Learn more by checking out their <a href="http://blog.stamps.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/complete-guide-usps-international-shipping.gif" target="_blank">international shipping infographic</a> or download their <a href="http://addons.prestashop.com/en/shipping-logistics-delivery-prestashop-modules/20185-stampsdotcom.html" target="_blank">free module</a> to jump right in and get started. </p>
<p><img src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2015/12/stamps-300x87.jpg" alt="stamps" width="155" class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-20946" /></p>
<h2 style="color:#01bad9">3. Meet new customers on marketplaces</h2>
<p>A great way to meet new potential customers is by listing your product on marketplaces like <a href="http://addons.prestashop.com/en/marketplace-prestashop-modules/2742-ebay.html" target="_blank">eBay</a>. You can choose to list your entire product catalog or just the most popular products. For customers who aren’t too familiar with your shop or brand, it’s a quick way to ease into purchasing from you. They can shop on a platform they are used to. The only difference is that this particular product is shipped by you. </p>
<p>Marketplaces are a great way for merchants looking to expand internationally to test out their target markets. Before making large investments into additional inventory for your new segment, listing your product on eBay can help you determine if there is even a need for that product in your target market. Learn more about how you can <a href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/how-to-harness-ebay-for-cross-border-sales/">harness eBay for cross-border sales</a> then download the <a href="http://addons.prestashop.com/en/marketplace-prestashop-modules/2742-ebay.html" target="_blank">free eBay module for PrestaShop</a> to get started. </p>
<p><img src="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/files/2015/12/ebay-300x123.jpg" alt="ebay" width="155" class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-20945" /></p>
<hr width="20%" align="left">
<p>Already selling internationally? What tactics and tips did you pick up? Share them in the comments below. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/3-tools-expand-business-internationally-2016/">3 tools to expand your business internationally in 2016</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en">EN - Ecommerce blog by PrestaShop</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.prestashop.com/blog/en/3-tools-expand-business-internationally-2016/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
