<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><modules><module><id><![CDATA[42]]></id><name><![CDATA[leguide]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[LeGuide.com]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Smart shopping]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Boost your sales and promote yourself to millions of online purchasers&nbsp;thanks to LeGuide]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/comparison-shopping-prestashop/42-leguidecom.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/42.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Boost your sales and promote yourself to millions of online purchasers&nbsp;thanks to LeGuide.com, the N&ordm;1 price comparison website in France and in Europe!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module allows you to export your product catalogue to the price comparison website leguide.com, the&nbsp;top independent French publisher of purchasing guides, shopping research engines and Internet price comparison websites, covering&nbsp;14 countries&nbsp;and with content published in&nbsp;nine languages. &nbsp;Gain visibility for your products&nbsp; It has 28.9 million unique visitors in Europe and any user can find your products when searching LeGuide and buy them directly in your online shop.  &nbsp; When you sell products online, customers must be able to find your site. Whether they want to track down an unusual product or simply identify the cheapest offer, shoppers usually use shopping guides. Referencing on a price comparison website is essential. &nbsp;Export your catalogue to LeGuide with a few clicks&nbsp; Our model allows you to export your products in a few stages thanks to its interface and simple, intuitive setup process! &nbsp;Gain qualified traffic so you can multiply your conversion rate&nbsp; Prospect for new customers getting ready to purchase among the tens of millions of Internet users built up by LeGuide in Europe and around the world. &nbsp; When Internet users search for your products at leguide.com, they are redirected to your shop in one click and can then buy your item there. That way you get full information about customers so you can start working to retain them straightaway! &nbsp;Increase your visibility abroad&nbsp; You can export your catalogue to all countries where LeGuide is available. &nbsp;LeGuide is one the best price comparison websites in terms of ROI.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[smart_shopping]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[119.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[139.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[89.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/595088-pprod/leguidecom.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595088-pbig/leguidecom.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[367]]></id><name><![CDATA[banipmod]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Ban IP addresses]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Administrative tools]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Ban unwelcome visitors from your shop]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/administration-tools-prestashop-modules/367-ban-ip-addresses.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/367.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Ban unwelcome visitors from your shop]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Protect your site from ill-intentioned visitors and unwanted bots]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/613667-pprod/ban-ip-addresses.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/613667-pbig/ban-ip-addresses.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1015]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedpack]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Pack 5 - Create ​​bundles of products]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Merchandising]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Allows the sale batch using any stocks actually available products composing your packs, and offers the opportunity to apply business operations]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/merchandising-prestashop-modules/1015-advanced-pack-5-create-bundles-of-products.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1015.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Allows the sale batch using any stocks actually available products composing your packs, and offers the opportunity to apply business operations.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Allow the purchase of combinations of products with or without a discount, in one click  Would you like to increase your average shopping cart and at the same time, allow your customers to save money if they purchase several products simultaneously? It is now possible thanks to&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;!  Without waiting any longer, you can create packs of products that can be purchased in one click, without worrying about stock or their combinations.  A precious additional sales tool  Accompany your customers in their buying process, by offering them&nbsp;packs of coherent products&nbsp;that you will have predefined, just as the salesman in a real shop would do. Such as for example: this fantastic camera, memory card and tripod. You know that this selection is appropriate and that it will appeal to your customers.  Or you could even use your best-sellers, by adding them to those that are less visible, to allow your customers to discover them.  Your packs will need to be made up of 2 products minimum, the number is unlimited. Push the quantity per product, choose the combinations of your choice, there are multiple options allowing you to multiply the possibilities.  Would you like to reserve the purchase of a product within a pack? That is also possible! You will therefore be able&nbsp;to offer a free product&nbsp;if it is purchased as part of a pack. The possibilities are infinite!  Integrated assistant  It isn&#39;t always obvious deciding which products should be offered within a pack. Here again&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;has the solution to the problem. When creating your pack, our module will supply you with strategic information, like the number of products sold or their available stock. There is also an integrated&nbsp;dynamic price simulator&nbsp;for your pack, to help you see more clearly when creating your business transaction, without you harming your profit margin.  Remain the maestro of combinations  One of the products that you have added to your pack is available in several colors, but you don&#39;t want to offer them all in this set? Advanced Pack&nbsp;will allow you to do this.  You will also have the possibility of predefining a combination by default, for each of the products of your pack, even if it&#39;s different to the one defined in your catalog.  Your customers will then be able to&nbsp;personalise their selection&nbsp;amongst the characteristics that you will have chosen to integrate in the offer.  Business Incentive  Incentive is something that motivates your visitor to make a purchase The main aim is to convince more of your site visitors to finish their order and/or&nbsp;spend more money per transaction. Perhaps you have already tried, by offering free delivery over a certain amount of purchases, or to offer discounts on certain products or even to send discount vouchers? All of these methods work, but their range is limited, as these promotions are usually temporary due to their excessive cost! Stop looking, you have already found the solution !  To entice your customers,&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;will give you the choice of applying a discount when all the products in the shopping cart are ordered, thus encouraging the purchase of the whole pack.  3 possibilities are available:&nbsp;Offer a specific discount on&nbsp;each product&nbsp;in the packApply a general discount on&nbsp;the set of productsApply a&nbsp;fixed price, such as a psychological price, for example Advanced Pack&nbsp;will also be able to manage the discounts already applied to your products, allowing you to integrate them in the pack price, or on the contrary, to exclude them, in order to choose the predefined discount on the pack. This decision will be made even easier thanks to our&nbsp;clear and clean-looking interface, that will allow you to see the discounted products very easily.  You won&#39;t need to worry about the coherence of your prices anymore  Have you ever had to review all the prices in your catalog, to detect any possible incoherences and correct them? What would happen if you had to manually manage the repercussions of these changes in product pricing in your packs? This would represent a significant extra workload if if it&#39;s not anticipated within the choice of management solutions within your packs!  Once again&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;has the solution.  By default, in the case where no reduction has been applied, the pack price is the sum of the products making it up. Should you need to modify the price of a product after having created the pack,&nbsp;the pack price will automatically be updated, and without you having to intervene.  In those cases where you will apply a discount to one or more products in an existing pack, and on condition you have authorized the&nbsp;promotional implications, the pack price will also be changed, showing your customers the discount that has been applied.  Is one of the products of your pack subject to an green-tax? No problem, it will automatically be reflected in the pack price and will be clearly stated, guaranteeing absolute&nbsp;respect for the legislation.  Regarding the management of your stock, everything has been automated!  For each pack ordered, the product stocks it contains will be&nbsp;automatically deducted. This way you will avoid the double management of stock or the frustration generated by sales rendered impossible, due to the bad assignation of quantities. Also, in the case where a product in a pack is out of stock, it will&nbsp;automatically be displayed as unavailable&nbsp;for purchase thanks to an availability warning system that is both elegant and modern.  For your customers, we have integrated a graphic and fun notification system, allowing the instant identification of stock shortages on combinations or products making up the pack.&nbsp;There&#39;s no chance of you receiving orders for products that are out of stock !  Highlight your packs and sell more  Once you have defined your pack, you will be able to configure it in the same way as you would a classic product. Everything is possible, such as assigning it customized images, classing it in the category of your choice,&nbsp;optimizing your SEO, writing a customized description, attributing it an EAN code or a specific reference, configuring its volume to calculate delivery costs, etc...  For those that are pressed for time, and in order to facilitate their marketing,&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;will automatically display all the photos of the products that make it up, as well as their descriptions, in the form of tabs. Your customers will be correctly informed, without leaving the page of your pack, and&nbsp;able to finalise their purchase in one click.  And that&#39;s not all... For more visibility, your packs will automatically be&nbsp;highlighted on their data sheets&nbsp;for those being sold in lots This way, you will encourage your customers to order the pack, rather than the product they were initially interested in. Essentially, this is&nbsp;cross-selling: an accessible method of&nbsp;increasing your average shopping cart&nbsp;!  We don&#39;t forget designers  From the beginning, we have integrated the fact that this module should be easily adapted by your web agency or designer/integrator. The module adapts itself perfectly to the default PrestaShop 1.5 and 1.6 themes, whilst allowing the most advanced graphic personalization.  A set of JavaScript templates and CSS style sheets are delivered as models with the module,&nbsp;to facilitate the integration process. Either yourself or your integrator will therefore be able to use all of the functionalities of the&nbsp;Advanced Pack 5&nbsp;engine, in order to present them in the graphic form that will best correspond with the general atmosphere of your online store.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.0.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[249.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[269.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/616235-pprod/advanced-pack-5-create-bundles-of-products.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/616235-pbig/advanced-pack-5-create-bundles-of-products.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1476]]></id><name><![CDATA[uspstracking]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[USPS Delivery Status]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Shipping & Delivery]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Offer your customers delivery via USPS, the essential e-commerce shipper, and view tracking information for your shipments directly from your PrestaShop back office]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/shipping-logistics-delivery-prestashop-modules/1476-usps-delivery-status.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1476.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Offer your customers delivery via USPS, the essential e-commerce shipper, and view tracking information for your shipments directly from your PrestaShop back office.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Improve trust in your site by offering shipments via USPS, the leading package delivery service in the United States.Optimize your conversions by offering quick and trackable delivery to your customers.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[100]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/634855-pprod/usps-delivery-status.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/634855-pbig/usps-delivery-status.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1504]]></id><name><![CDATA[upstrackingv2]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[UPS Delivery Status]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Shipping & Delivery]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Do you deliver with UPS, a company known for its speed and reliability?  With the UPS Tracking module, make your life even easier by tracking your UPS shipments directly from your Back-Office and impr]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/shipping-logistics-delivery-prestashop-modules/1504-ups-delivery-status.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1504.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Do you deliver with UPS, a company known for its speed and reliability?  With the UPS Tracking module, make your life even easier by tracking your UPS shipments directly from your Back-Office and improve customer&rsquo;s satisfaction by automatically sending update emails to your clients when their order status has changed.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Take advantage of the UPS Tracking module: &nbsp;Get advanced tracking for your shipments, step by step, straight from your Back OfficeImprove your customers&rsquo; overall purchasing experience by regularly informing them about their order status and delivery of their package&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/611439-pprod/ups-delivery-status.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/611439-pbig/ups-delivery-status.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1615]]></id><name><![CDATA[gshopping]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Google Shopping (Merchant Center)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Smart shopping]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Increase your sales by at least 30% by including your products in Google Shopping and introduce yourself to the millions of online shoppers who use Google!&nbsp;  &nbsp;]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/comparison-shopping-prestashop/1615-google-shopping-merchant-center.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1615.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Increase your sales by at least 30% by including your products in Google Shopping and introduce yourself to the millions of online shoppers who use Google!&nbsp;  &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increase visits to your shop&nbsp; 80 million product searches in Google! When you register your products, all users will be able to find them when they search with Google and buy them directly from your online shop. You can also find new customers using Google Shopping apps for tablets and mobile devices. &nbsp;Save time&nbsp; Our module allows you to export your products to Google Shopping as simply as possible. Quick, intuitive, easy-to-use interface. &nbsp;Increase your conversion rate using Google qualified traffic&nbsp; Visitors arriving from Google Shopping have selected your product from the images available... so they are ready to buy. &nbsp;Improve the positioning of your shop on the search engine by using Google tools&nbsp;Increase your international visibility.&nbsp; You can export your catalogue in various currencies to publicise your products to consumers in all the countries where Google Shopping is present. &nbsp;Google Shopping is one of the marketplaces with best return on investment.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[smart_shopping]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.1.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[129.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[149.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[99.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/708922-pprod/google-shopping-merchant-center.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/708922-pbig/google-shopping-merchant-center.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2501]]></id><name><![CDATA[amazon]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Amazon Market Place]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marketplace & Affiliation Platforms]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Exclusive PrestaShop Addons, the Amazon Market Place module is the #1 solution to export products on Amazon, import and manage orders from the marketplace]]></description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/marketplace-prestashop-modules/2501-amazon-market-place.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2501.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Exclusive PrestaShop Addons, the Amazon Market Place module is the #1 solution to export products on Amazon, import and manage orders from the marketplace.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[You can easily integrate your PrestaShop store to the world’s top marketplace and significantly increase your sales. You import your orders into your PrestaShop store and centralize your stocks.  Managing your inventory efficiently and quickly honoring your Amazon orders allows you to increase the degree of customer satisfaction and thus automatically increase the rank of your seller performance.  The design of the module is based on the initial experience of online retailers. The module was developed by an online retailer for the service of his colleagues and it was developed by a team of professional developers, by making it easy to use and to have the maximum efficiency.  Your purchase is protected by free technical support that is provided unconditionally until the products are placed online and the first orders are imported.  This module was developed by Common-Services, which is a partner agency of Prestashop. Common-Services has been featuring on PrestaShop Addons  since 2010 and it has also published 15 other best-selling modules that are marketed only on PrestaShop Addons.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.1.138]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[279.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[164.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/686436-pprod/amazon-market-place.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/686436-pbig/amazon-market-place.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2778]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedsearch4]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Search 4]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Search & Filter]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Best Module Award Winner -&nbsp;Add the fastest layered navigation system for PrestaShop !]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/search-filters-prestashop-modules/2778-advanced-search-4.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2778.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Best Module Award Winner -&nbsp;Add the fastest layered navigation system for PrestaShop !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Provide to your customers the products that meet their needs.  Indispensable tool for shops offering a wide selection of products,&nbsp;Advanced Search 4&nbsp;can add as many search engines as you want and place them in different places on your website. This module was developed in an effort to provide short loading times, even on large catalogs. Your visitors can browse products that match their search criteria, to make their purchases in minimal time.  Winner of the Best PrestaShop Modules Awards 2012  Advanced Search 4 won the&nbsp;Best module&nbsp;of the year Award at the PrestaShop BarCamp of Barcelona (Spain)!  Indispensable tool for shops offering a wide selection of products.  Advanced Search 4&nbsp;adds the multi-layered navigation, search by step, filters and multi-criteria searches. Each search is saved over the navigation, allowing your visitors to return to the results of their research at any time.  Google is his friend  This PrestaShop Addon is a small revolution for SEO. Advanced Search 4 generate a mass-produced products pages optimized for SEO, and without duplicate content! Pick up your criteria on which you want to improve your SEO, validate them, and here you go with hundreds of pages listing your products, including: re-written URL, H1 tags, description, meta tags, automatised cross links...&nbsp;  To maximize your reputation, these results pages can be shared on most social networks places around the internet, as well as sent by e-mail.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.10.17]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[279.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[164.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/573189-pprod/advanced-search-4.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/573189-pbig/advanced-search-4.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2792]]></id><name><![CDATA[dmuassocprodcat]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[DMU Association flash Products / Categories]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Quick / Mass Edit]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[An essential module for your products! You have over than 100 products? You want to control the association of your products to your categories? This module is for you!]]></description><author><![CDATA[Dream Me Up]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/bulk-update-prestashop-modules/2792-dmu-association-flash-products-categories.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2792.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[An essential module for your products! You have over than 100 products? You want to control the association of your products to your categories? This module is for you!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save time! In one interface, all in ajax (without reloading the page), see the products associated to a category. Look for products that you want to add this category and add 1 click! You also control the default category of your products directly through the icon on the right.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[quick_bulk_update]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/51759-pprod/dmu-association-flash-products-categories.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/51759-pbig/dmu-association-flash-products-categories.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2937]]></id><name><![CDATA[storemanagerforprestashop]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Store Manager for PrestaShop]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Administrative tools]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[30-DAY FREE TRIAL!&nbsp;&nbsp;The back office solution you need to run your PrestaShop online store efficiently ! Store Manager for PrestaShop&nbsp;will save you over 2 hours a day by automating daily]]></description><author><![CDATA[eMagicOne]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/administration-tools-prestashop-modules/2937-store-manager-for-prestashop.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2937.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[30-DAY FREE TRIAL!&nbsp;&nbsp;The back office solution you need to run your PrestaShop online store efficiently ! Store Manager for PrestaShop&nbsp;will save you over 2 hours a day by automating daily tasks&nbsp;and making it simple to update your shop. &nbsp; Store Manager for PrestaShop is a desktop application, designed to speed up and automate the management of PrestaShop based stores. Not only does it take care of the mass operations with products, categories, orders and customers extending the functionality of the store web back-end, but also lines up with an intuitive interface and advanced addons for easy store management. Save your time, money, and resources by allowing Store Manager for PrestaShop do all the job for you. Store Manager for PrestaShop will make your store stand out from the crowd! &nbsp; *** WINNER OF THE PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE *** &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save your time, money, and resources by allowing Store Manager for PrestaShop do all the job for you. Store Manager for PrestaShop will make your store stand out from the crowd! &nbsp; Spend an Hour, Save a Day! Store Manager for PrestaShop was designed to work for you and not at the expense of your business. It is your personal assistant that does all the routine tasks, saving you tons of time for greater deeds. For that matter, it provides with ready-made export/import features, report tools, advanced addons, etc. No need to spend a day getting deep into how your store works, spend an hour understanding how Store Manager does the job for you. &nbsp; Take Your Online Business to the Bank Buy one Store Manager instead of multiple modules. Use one Store Manager license to manage your multiple stores. Store Manager doesn&rsquo;t require any special skills, so you don&rsquo;t have to pay someone to keep your store database organized. You can implement all the necessary updates yourself with Store Manager for PrestaShop and get on to important tasks. &nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[]]></version><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/689783-pprod/store-manager-for-prestashop.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/689783-pbig/store-manager-for-prestashop.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[3162]]></id><name><![CDATA[webcallback]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Call Back]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Front office features]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Add the Call Back module to your online store to increase sales!  Nothing is more frustrating than getting through to a company, just to be put on hold]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/3162-web-call-back.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3162.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Add the Call Back module to your online store to increase sales!  Nothing is more frustrating than getting through to a company, just to be put on hold. Stop wasting customers&rsquo; time with the Call Back Module. Let customers leave their contact information for you to contact them at a convenient time. Capture customers you would have otherwise lost.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[24.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/611422-pprod/web-call-back.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/611422-pbig/web-call-back.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[3252]]></id><name><![CDATA[printlabels]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Print Labels Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Administrative tools]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Save valuable time by automating the preparation of your delivery labels! Prepare and print your delivery labels, and stick them right on the packages for the orders you&#39;re shipping]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/administration-tools-prestashop-modules/3252-print-labels.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3252.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Save valuable time by automating the preparation of your delivery labels! Prepare and print your delivery labels, and stick them right on the packages for the orders you&#39;re shipping.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save time shipping your ordersLower your rate of returned packages due to wrong addresses]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.2.8]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595260-pprod/print-labels.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/595260-pbig/print-labels.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[3438]]></id><name><![CDATA[auctions]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Auctions]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Front office features]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Auctions module was created to give merchants ability to sell products on auctions in easiest possible way]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/3438-auctions.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3438.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Auctions module was created to give merchants ability to sell products on auctions in easiest possible way. With a number of great features and intuitive interface, this is the best auctions module available for Prestashop.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module was created to give merchants ability to sell products on auctions in easiest possible way. Auctions are the great way to attract and keep customers in your shop. You will be sure that customer is paying right price for your products. You don't have to negotiate prices with customers anymore. Managing auctions is very intuitive, and fully integrated with your shop. You will feel like it's not a module but integral part of the PrestaShop.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[29.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/625145-pprod/auctions.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/625145-pbig/auctions.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[3511]]></id><name><![CDATA[priceminister]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PriceMinister]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marketplace & Affiliation Platforms]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Take advantage of the PriceMinister audience with its 2 million visitors a year and its 20 million subscribed members and boost your sales with your super PriceMinister store]]></description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/marketplace-prestashop-modules/3511-priceminister.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3511.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Take advantage of the PriceMinister audience with its 2 million visitors a year and its 20 million subscribed members and boost your sales with your super PriceMinister store.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With the PriceMinister for Prestashop module, your processing is automated, the products are exported directly to the PriceMinister marketplace and your orders are automatically imported and integrated into your Prestashop store.   You also automate communication with your customers: your order confirmations are sent directly to the customer by email via the PriceMinister web service, customers are automatically notified and the status of your orders is automatically updated.  By using the PriceMinister module, you maintain control of your offer and product flows, you automatically import your orders without additional cost or subscription and your data exchanges are automated and free.  Integration is easy and convenient: you configure your module, your export becomes automatic and so you have no more data to manipulate  Implementing scheduled tasks is simple and automated thanks to compatibility with the Prestashop Cron task-scheduling editor module (free). Just click on a button to automatically integrate your scheduled tasks in the module. It is still possible to manually configure your tasks.  The module design is based on the online merchant experience. The module was conceived by an online merchant in the service of his colleagues and developed by professional developers, which gives it ease of use and maximum effectiveness.  Your purchase is protected by free technical support which is assured unconditionally up to the moment of making the products available online and the import of your first orders.  You must have a PriceMinister PRO account.  New version, PriceMinister v4: export XML, simplified configuration, native scheduled tasks, intelligent mapping, sleek design and improved ergonomics.  This module was developed by Common-Services, which is a partner agency of Prestashop. Common-Services has been featuring on PrestaShop Addons since 2010 and it has also published 15 other best-selling modules that are marketed only on PrestaShop Addons.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.0.15]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[174.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[114.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[4414]]></id><name><![CDATA[allinone_rewards]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[All-in-one Rewards: loyalty sponsorship affiliation FB]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Advertising & Marketing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Allows your customers to earn rewards, all grouped into a single account, while developing SEO and reputation of your shop: loyalty program, sponsorship (multilevel, self-promotional), affiliation, fa]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/advertising-marketing-newsletter-modules/4414-all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation-fb.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4414.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Allows your customers to earn rewards, all grouped into a single account, while developing SEO and reputation of your shop: loyalty program, sponsorship (multilevel, self-promotional), affiliation, facebook and more. Your sales will really increase !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get tons of new customers and increase your brand reputation thanks to the All-in-one Rewards module !  This module allows to set up a complete system of rewards in your shop to increase SEO and reputation thanks to the virality of the system, and to follow very precisely the performance.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[279.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[164.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/awards-loyalty.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/617761-pprod/all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation-fb.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/617761-pbig/all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation-fb.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4549]]></id><name><![CDATA[dmurealtimestats]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[DMU Real Time Statistics]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Analytics & Stats]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Visualize in Real Time every visitor on your shop ! With this module you are no longer blind ! you are able to know everything about the activity of your shop]]></description><author><![CDATA[Dream Me Up]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/analytics-stats-prestashop-modules/4549-dmu-real-time-statistics.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4549.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Visualize in Real Time every visitor on your shop ! With this module you are no longer blind ! you are able to know everything about the activity of your shop.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module lets you know exactly what is happening on your shop. Now you are able to visualize the path of a visitor, his reactions on each page visited, ease or blocking steps in the ordering process ...  ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[64.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/324796-pprod/dmu-real-time-statistics.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/324796-pbig/dmu-real-time-statistics.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4932]]></id><name><![CDATA[mynewsletter]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Newsletter & Statistics]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Advertising & Marketing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The best way to convert, build loyalty and keep in touch with customers is with our Newsletter with Statistics Module! This brilliant module helps you send gorgeous newsletters to customer groups -- a]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/advertising-marketing-newsletter-modules/4932-newsletter-statistics.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4932.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The best way to convert, build loyalty and keep in touch with customers is with our Newsletter with Statistics Module! This brilliant module helps you send gorgeous newsletters to customer groups -- and help keep them coming back to shop!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Track the effectiveness of each newsletter. Every KPI you, as an online merchant, should monitor is available at your fingertips. These key statistics allow online merchants to monitor newsletters to see which work and which don&rsquo;t to improve newsletter mailings.  Additional benefits include:Inform customers about sales, company or industry news, new products, etc.Personalize newsletters (to echo your brand identity)Build customer loyalty to your brandStay in touch with your customers]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.0.25]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.5.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[139.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595046-pprod/newsletter-statistics.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/595046-pbig/newsletter-statistics.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4982]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_seointernallinking]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Internal Linking]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Improve your SEO through internal linking strategy]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/seo-prestashop-modules/4982-seo-internal-linking.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4982.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Improve your SEO through internal linking strategy]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Enhance your PrestaShop SEO  Internal linking&nbsp;is the creation of links between pages of your shop, using keywords you want to achieve a&nbsp;better place on Google.  To&nbsp;optimize the SEO of your website, it is essential to create an&nbsp;internal linking&nbsp;that will allow search engines to browse your shop in the most easy way as possible. The goal is to provide maximum informations with the least clicks deep.  SEO Internal Linking&nbsp;PrestaShop module optimizes the organization of navigation in your store, and plays an essential role in your&nbsp;SEO strategy.  Define the keywords on which you wish to be listed and their landing pages, and let the module create the links for you!  If you want to add automatic links in your categories descriptions, consider installing our PrestaShop module&nbsp;HTML On Descriptions.  Do we really need internal linking?  Internal linking strategy&nbsp;based on specific keywords is an optimization method that has proven its worth. Especially to enhance a content relevance.  Among the disadvantages, you should know that the installation of these links is long and tedious, and requires to&nbsp;follow SEO good practices, to not over-optimize (which would be detected by Google), and must be updated regularly to track changes in your catalog.  With this in mind, we have developed this module, allowing you to deploy thousands of cross links between your pages within minutes, while being sure to observe best practice guidelines of White Hat SEO.  It has been designed to support both SEO agencies and e-shop owners. SEO Internal Linking&nbsp;is really simple to manage.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.11]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.3.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[204.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[124.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573343-pprod/seo-internal-linking.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573343-pbig/seo-internal-linking.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[5255]]></id><name><![CDATA[ordertaxprofitreport]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Analytics & Stats]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Create professional sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports in HTML format or export as a CSV / Excel file]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/analytics-stats-prestashop-modules/5255-advanced-sales-tax-profit-and-profit-margin-reports.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/5255.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Create professional sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports in HTML format or export as a CSV / Excel file.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get perfect visibility on your shop&#39;s and products&#39; profitability !  The default PrestaShop installation does not provide a one-click tool that allows you to obtain important accounting and financial data: tax due, net sales volume after discounts and, most importantly,&nbsp;profit and profit margin.  Not only will this report provide you with all this data, but it will even allow you to answer questions like &quot;what percentage of total sales and / or profits does this specific brand, supplier or product category represent ?&quot;.  This stylish and pleasant AJAX based module allows you to generate different types of preformed reports with all this information. They can be viewed on screen in HTML format or exported as a CSV&nbsp;file to manipulate in Excel and / or import into any other information or accounting system.  This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011 PrestaShop Awards for Best module.    You are guaranteed to buy a quality module and to get fast and efficient tech support in case you need it.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.9.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.3.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[204.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[119.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/543344-pprod/advanced-sales-tax-profit-and-profit-margin-reports.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/543344-pbig/advanced-sales-tax-profit-and-profit-margin-reports.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[5275]]></id><name><![CDATA[productsbycategoryslider]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Slider - Products of same category]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Slideshows]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Submit items of the same class on your product pages with this slider at the bottom of the page, and improve the navigation of your customers, along with your average basket!]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/slideshows-prestashop-modules/5275-slider-products-of-same-category.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/5275.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Submit items of the same class on your product pages with this slider at the bottom of the page, and improve the navigation of your customers, along with your average basket!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module allows you to make cross-selling of other products in each category, and increase your average shopping basket.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[slideshows]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/625266-pprod/slider-products-of-same-category.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/625266-pbig/slider-products-of-same-category.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[5314]]></id><name><![CDATA[npaypalpro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PayPal Direct Payments]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payments & Gateways]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[PayPal is one of the world&#39;s most trusted online payment solutions. The PayPal Direct Payment Module allows you to start accepting credit card transactions immediately]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/payments-gateways-prestashop-modules/5314-paypal-direct-payments.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/5314.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[PayPal is one of the world&#39;s most trusted online payment solutions. The PayPal Direct Payment Module allows you to start accepting credit card transactions immediately. With the PayPal Direct Payment module, create a streamlined checkout process that allows customers to pay for products online with a simple click of the mouse.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Paypal Direct Payment is the solution tailored to your business:Simply configure your Client ID and Secret key.Accept payments in 21 currencies from 190 countries around the globe.Industry-leading fraud and buyer protections keep you and your customers safe.There are no setup fees or long-term contracts.Supports One-page checkout (PrestaShop native&nbsp;feature).&nbsp; The combination of PrestaShop expertise and Paypal Direct Payment services is the perfect solution to sell online.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[179.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[204.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/689459-pprod/paypal-direct-payments.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/689459-pbig/paypal-direct-payments.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[5542]]></id><name><![CDATA[orderpreparation]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Easy order preparation]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Administrative tools]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Save precious minutes every day by optimizing your logistics]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/administration-tools-prestashop-modules/5542-easy-order-preparation.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/5542.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Save precious minutes every day by optimizing your logistics.&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save timeSimplify your logistics]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[24.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/613679-pprod/easy-order-preparation.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/613679-pbig/easy-order-preparation.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6059]]></id><name><![CDATA[cdiscount]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cdiscount Marketplace]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marketplace & Affiliation Platforms]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Sell your products on the Cdiscount marketplace: catalogue export, automatic updating of prices and stocks, retrieval and management of orders]]></description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/marketplace-prestashop-modules/6059-cdiscount-marketplace.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6059.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Sell your products on the Cdiscount marketplace: catalogue export, automatic updating of prices and stocks, retrieval and management of orders. Beneficiate from 3-month subscription free when you register on Cdiscount !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[C Le Marché is one of France’s leading marketplaces.  Boost your sales! Make the most of the traffic generated by Cdiscount to sell your products and enjoy the numerous advantages which make Cdiscount such a success: - payment in 4 instalments (fully supported by Cdiscount) - multiple delivery methods, etc.  Cdiscount takes care of everything! Place your products for sale on the marketplace and manage your orders while Cdiscount takes care of the rest: traffic, easy and secure payment, marketing, etc.  1 single back office! Thanks to the Cdiscount for PrestaShop module, you no longer need to manage several different back offices. In just a few clicks, connect your PrestaShop site to your Cdiscount store and post your products: - Product descriptions are exported directly to the Cdiscount marketplace, - Prices and inventories are automatically updated, - Your orders will be directly imported and integrated into your PrestaShop store.  Practical and easy configuration! Once you have configured your module, exports are automatic meaning you no longer have any data to handle.  A module developed by an e-merchant for e-merchants! The module’s design is based on the early experience of online retailers. It was created by an e-merchants for the benefit of fellow e-merchants and developed by a team of professional developers, resulting in maximum user friendliness and efficiency.  Free technical support! Your purchase is guaranteed by free technical support provided unconditionally until your products are placed online and your first orders are imported.   *This offer applies for merchants already registered on CleMarché Marketplace and cannot be used in combination with any other ongoing Cdiscount.com offer.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.9.145]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[194.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[119.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/715585-pprod/cdiscount-marketplace.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/715585-pbig/cdiscount-marketplace.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6291]]></id><name><![CDATA[siretcustomergroup]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SIRET and customer group]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Front office features]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Differentiate your business customers of individuals with this SIRET module which transfers the professionals in a given customer group]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/6291-siret-and-customer-group.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6291.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Differentiate your business customers of individuals with this SIRET module which transfers the professionals in a given customer group.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Finally, you can easily manage your professional customers just by asking their SIRET to transfer them in a client group or there is no tax for example, with prices reduced (e.g. wholesalers)...]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/101289-pprod/siret-and-customer-group.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/101289-pbig/siret-and-customer-group.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6356]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_multiplefeatures]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Multiple Features - Assign your features as you want]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Search & Filter]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Multiple Features allows you to assign multiple values ​​of features to your products]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/search-filters-prestashop-modules/6356-multiple-features-assign-your-features-as-you-want.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6356.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Multiple Features allows you to assign multiple values ​​of features to your products]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Add features to your PrestaShop catalog without limits!  With&nbsp;Multiple Features, you can assign as many values as necessary for the same product and the same feature. Remove this PrestaShop limitation and start using your features as you want!  If you also use our layered navigation system&nbsp;Advanced Search 4&nbsp;(Winner of PrestaShop Best Module Awards 2012), you can give to your customers a more relevant research in your catalog.  Customer study :  Ocarat.com: &quot;Some jewelry may have a different composition and an alloy of several metals. PrestaShop provides the ability to associate a feature to a product. However, I want to integrate in my shop a gold ring set with diamonds and emeralds. But features tab does not allow me to do so. I can&#39;t assign multiple values to a single purpose. So I have to choose between gold, diamonds or emeralds.&nbsp;Multiple Features remove PrestaShop limits and allows you to use features as you want !&quot;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.9.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[29.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573403-pprod/multiple-features-assign-your-features-as-you-want.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/573403-pbig/multiple-features-assign-your-features-as-you-want.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6413]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_cachemanager]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cache Manager]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Decrease your loading page time generation]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/seo-prestashop-modules/6413-cache-manager.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6413.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Decrease your loading page time generation]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Improve your conversion rate and SEO  The statistics are clear: the main reason why a user leave a web page is the loading time.  Yahoo! said that adding 400ms to the page loading time on their car website raises the dropout rate from 5 to 9%. (Sources: Performance Web)  In addition, the speed display is a guarantee of quality which has a very positive influence on the positioning in the search engines.  Let your customers enjoy a more comfortable navigation on your website by shortening the loading time of pages, and saving his time!  Limited offer : Price drop &amp; Satisfied or refunded !]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.12]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573569-pprod/cache-manager.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/573569-pbig/cache-manager.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6414]]></id><name><![CDATA[lgabonos]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Credit Notes / Memos of the Complete Invoice in PDF]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Billing & Invoicing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Generate credit notes of the full invoice you need to cancel (not possible to generate partial credit notes). Unlimited number of credit notes]]></description><author><![CDATA[Línea Gráfica]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/billing-invoicing-prestashop-modules/6414-credit-notes-memos-of-the-complete-invoice-in-pdf.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6414.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Generate credit notes of the full invoice you need to cancel (not possible to generate partial credit notes). Unlimited number of credit notes. Issue the notes in PDF format and send them to your customers.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[TO READ BEFORE PURCHASING THE MODULE Our module is only able to issue full credit notes (not possible to generate partial credit notes). Each credit note generated by our module automatically cancels the whole order, it's not possible to generate partial credit notes for just some products of the order. If you need partial credit notes, you can cancel the whole invoice with our module and place a new order afterwards.  Easily generate credit notes of the full invoice This module allows you to generate full credit notes for any invoices that have been issued and then cancelled. The module is very easy to use: select the order number you want to cancel and click on the button "Create". Then click on the PDF icon to download/open it.  PDF credit notes The module creates credit notes in PDF format that you can easily send to your clients. Each credit notes contains:the store logothe billing and delivery addressthe credit note details (issued date and number)the order details (date, number, payment method and carrier)the ordered products (name, attributes, reference, unit price tax excl., unit price incl., discount, quantity and total tax incl.)the total calculation (product total tax excl., product total tax incl., shipping cost, total tax and total)]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[billing_invoicing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.5.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[99.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[59.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/691071-pprod/credit-notes-memos-of-the-complete-invoice-in-pdf.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/691071-pbig/credit-notes-memos-of-the-complete-invoice-in-pdf.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[7152]]></id><name><![CDATA[customfields]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Custom Fields]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Content Management]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Create unlimited number of custom fields for registration form. You can add all kinds of fields: text, text area, radio buttons, check boxes and select lists with unlimited number of options and more]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/content-management/7152-custom-fields.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/7152.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Create unlimited number of custom fields for registration form. You can add all kinds of fields: text, text area, radio buttons, check boxes and select lists with unlimited number of options and more.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[It's important to know about as much as possible about customers. It will help with better understanding of the clients habits and needs. That knowledge will allow e-merchant to improve it's services and finally make more profit of his business. Custom fields module in easy way allows you to create unlimited number of custom fields and get all required data about your customers that cannot be done with standard registration form. All fields can be validated with selected validation rule and can be viewed and editable in the backoffice.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[content_management]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/582276-pprod/custom-fields.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/582276-pbig/custom-fields.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[7422]]></id><name><![CDATA[groupinc]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Price increment/discount by customer groups]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Front office features]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module lets you apply an increment or a discount to product price depending on the customer's group]]></description><author><![CDATA[Idnovate]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/7422-price-increment-discount-by-customer-groups.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/7422.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module lets you apply an increment or a discount to product price depending on the customer's group.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Apply different price to the product depending on the group that customer belongs toApply a markup to your products]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[24.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/569002-pprod/price-increment-discount-by-customer-groups.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/569002-pbig/price-increment-discount-by-customer-groups.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8244]]></id><name><![CDATA[ec_seo404]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO - disabled and deleted 301 redirect Products]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[End with 404 pages and referencing loss for disabled or deleted product]]></description><author><![CDATA[Ether Création]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/seo-prestashop-modules/8244-seo-disabled-and-deleted-301-redirect-products.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/8244.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[End with 404 pages and referencing loss for disabled or deleted product. You will be able to choose for each case a 301, 302 redirection, home page or default category (Ideal for SEO)]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Whenever a product will be deactivated or deleted, you will be able to assign a redirect (permanent: 301 not found: 404 temporary: 302, an url internal or external to your web site, the home page of your site or default category).  No need to turn your catalog to know what your pages are no longer valid link, the module will tell you. And this whatever the language or the store (if multi-boutique). In addition, you can manually add a link of your choice. You can edit multiple products at the same time to save time if the rule is the same (parent category, home, etc ...)  You can define rules that will, in the future, when a product is disabled / deleted, created a redirection to a desired page.  When a product is reactivated, forwarding rules automatically deactivate.  Not overload your HTACCESS file and therefore no notion necessary to make it work, or any slowdown in browsing your site.  All referrals are importable one by one or en masse from a csv file whose example is provided.  So your referenced links will be redirected with confidence to not lose your positioning.  Through a system of colors, get a look to the status of your referrals to know what will or not : - White => redirection is active! - Green => as possible redirection for disabled or deleted page but the redirection is not active. - Orange => can Redirection for disabled or deleted page but the redirection is not active and no link is entered for the redirection. - Grey => redirection is inactive because the page has been reactivated. - Red => Redirection enabled, but not here! So page 404 usual!  You also get a filter system depending on the state (broken links, error redirection, redirection to, etc ...) in order to act accordingly quickly.  With this module no more broken links on your site!  Two other augmented versions of the modules exist : -  one with category page more : http://addons.prestashop.com/en/seo-prestashop-modules/11258-seo-404-301-product-and-category-delete-or-disable.html  - The other pages with categories, brands, founisseurs, cms and specific urls! http://addons.prestashop.com/en/seo-prestashop-modules/18272-301-seo-automatic-redirection-of-all-your-404.html  ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/683583-pprod/seo-disabled-and-deleted-301-redirect-products.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/683583-pbig/seo-disabled-and-deleted-301-redirect-products.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8458]]></id><name><![CDATA[wic_pushproductcms]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Push Products on CMS Pages]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Merchandising]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module allows you to display a block with the products you want on your CMS pages]]></description><author><![CDATA[Web In Color]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/merchandising-prestashop-modules/8458-push-products-on-cms-pages.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/8458.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module allows you to display a block with the products you want on your CMS pages. Use all the pages of your website and increase your sales!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module oriented Merchandising allows you to optimize all your pages, including these you thought it was not possible (Shipping, Secure Payment, Legals, etc..)Highlight a selection of products on your CMS pages.Configure these products by CMS pages directly from your back office easely.Increase your sales.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[64.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/582794-pprod/push-products-on-cms-pages.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/582794-pbig/push-products-on-cms-pages.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8734]]></id><name><![CDATA[lgcookieslaw]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[EU Cookie Law (Notification Banner + Cookie Blocker)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Front office features]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The only module that allows you to fully comply with the EU cookie law. Display a responsive and custom warning banner and disable cookies when users enter your website until you obtain their consent]]></description><author><![CDATA[Línea Gráfica]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/8734-eu-cookie-law-notification-banner-cookie-blocker.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/8734.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The only module that allows you to fully comply with the EU cookie law. Display a responsive and custom warning banner and disable cookies when users enter your website until you obtain their consent.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Our module fully complies with the European Cookie Law.  Complete compliance with the law  Besides displaying a warning banner, our module is the only one that allows you to block the cookies when users enter your store. As established by the law, you "shall ensure that the storing of information, or the gaining of access to information already stored, in the terminal equipment of a subscriber or user is only allowed on condition that the subscriber or user concerned has given his or her consent, having been provided with clear and comprehensive information."  Please note that all the other cookie modules sold on Addons only allows you to display a warning banner regardless of the user consent. Cookies are installed on the users' computer without obtaining their consent and regardless of their will.  Main features of the modulesDisplay a warning banner on every page to inform users about the use of cookies and ask for their consentDisable a list of modules when users enter the website because warning users about cookies is useless and illegal if you have already installed cookies on their computer.Enable these cookies after having obtained their consent or maintain them disabled if they refuse.Fully customize the warning banner (color, text, link, font, position, multilingual mode, transparency, buttons...) Getting the user consent   The module includes 2 different ways to ask user consent, you can choose between:Acceptance through a button: Users must click on the "I accept" button in the warning banner to give his consent. As soon as users give their consent, the warning banner disappears and all the modules using cookies will get enabled and will work as usual. But if users refuse to give their consent, the disabled modules will remain disabled. We recommend you to use this mode, this one allows you to fully comply with the law.Acceptance through the navigation: If users continue browsing the website, they will accept the use of cookies. The warning banner is displayed on the first page on which users arrive with a message like « By continuing browsing the website, you accept the use of cookies ». As soon as users decide to go to another page, the banner automatically disappears and the disabled modules will get enabled.Note: the consent remains valid during the period of time set in the module interface (we recommend you not to go over 13 months)  Customizing the banner content and design  As recommended by the European authority, the module allows you to customize the warning message inside the banner (to inform users about the cookies users and their purpose) and add a "More information" button into the banner that take users to a CMS page of your store (to explain in details the use of cookies on your store).  The warning banner is responsive and will always be displayed full-width. The module comes with a Wysiwyg editor that allows you to fully customize the content of the banner (font, color, effects, html code, links...). You can also choose from the configuration page the background color of the banner, its percentage of opacity (transparency) and its position (top or bottom of the page). Moreover, the module is multilingual and automatically detects all the languages of your store, which allows you to set a different warning message per language.  Note: the module is designed to not display a warning message when search engines robots crawl you store in order not to affect your SEO.  Disabling the modules that use cookies  This is the only module that allows you to choose the modules/cookies that you want to disable until users give their consent. This feature is compulsory because it is useless and illegal to inform users if you have already installed cookies on their computer with their consent.  "Member States shall ensure that the storing of information, or the gaining of access to information already stored, in the terminal equipment of a subscriber or user is only allowed on condition that the subscriber or user concerned has given his or her consent, having been provided with clear and comprehensive information, in accordance with Directive 95/46/EC” EU Cookie Law  To comply with the directive of the EU Cookie Law, we recommend you to disable the tracking (Google Analytics), social sharing (Facebook " Like ", Google " +1 ", etc.) and targeted advertising modules. Please note that all modules that are required for the good running of your PrestaShop store (ex: basket cookie, session cookie...) don't require any consents.  Multistore mode  The module is compatible with multistore and allows you to display the same notification banner on each one of your shop but the consent is the same for all shops. If you accept the use of cookies on one of your shop, the module will consider that you accept the use of cookies for all your other shops (mention it on your cookie policy) and the notification banner will not be shown when you go to your other shops.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[34.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[24.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/689395-pprod/eu-cookie-law-notification-banner-cookie-blocker.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/689395-pbig/eu-cookie-law-notification-banner-cookie-blocker.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8741]]></id><name><![CDATA[dmulistecommandes]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[DMU Improved Order List]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Administrative tools]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Save time on the processing of your orders! Avoid having to enter each command one after the other for all the details. This module lets you know everything from your order list]]></description><author><![CDATA[Dream Me Up]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/administration-tools-prestashop-modules/8741-dmu-improved-order-list.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/8741.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Save time on the processing of your orders! Avoid having to enter each command one after the other for all the details. This module lets you know everything from your order list.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[The more you have order to process and the more this module will save you time. As much by the fact that all information is available from the command list and because you will be able to change status in mass with this module.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.9]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[99.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[59.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/543848-pprod/dmu-improved-order-list.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/543848-pbig/dmu-improved-order-list.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[9783]]></id><name><![CDATA[gtrustedstores]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Google Trusted Stores]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Advertising & Marketing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Become a Google Trusted Stores certified merchant and let your customers benefit from Google&rsquo;s new and free e-commerce services. Conversion rate and repeat purchase increase guaranteed]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/advertising-marketing-newsletter-modules/9783-google-trusted-stores.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/9783.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Become a Google Trusted Stores certified merchant and let your customers benefit from Google&rsquo;s new and free e-commerce services. Conversion rate and repeat purchase increase guaranteed.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Reassure your customers and increase your conversion rate and sales on your PrestaShop website by becoming a certified Google Trusted Stores merchant and be part of Google&rsquo;s latest e-commerce service.  By using this module in conjunction with our Google Merchant Center module (available separately on http://addons.prestashop.com/en/seo-prestashop-modules/1768-Google-Merchant-Center.html), you will get the best possible results on the PrestaShop e-commerce platform.  This module is developed and published by Business Tech, Platinum Certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011 PrestaShop Awards for Best module.  You are guaranteed to buy a quality module and to get fast and efficient tech support in case you need it.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[129.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[79.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/559340-pprod/google-trusted-stores.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/559340-pbig/google-trusted-stores.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[11345]]></id><name><![CDATA[pushoncart]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Push on Cart (Upselling)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Prices & Promotion]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Easily increase your average cart value by offering customized discounts to your client in the shopping cart summary !]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/pricing-promotion-prestashop-modules/11345-push-on-cart-upselling.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/11345.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Easily increase your average cart value by offering customized discounts to your client in the shopping cart summary !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With the Push on Cart module:Easily increase your customer&rsquo;s average cart valueClear unsold products from your inventoryGet your customers to discover new products to create a need and even secure their loyaltyCreate demand for new productsCapitalize on impulse purchasesImprove customer satisfaction and loyalty with customized discounts on select products Push on cart User Reviews:&nbsp; Comment&nbsp;posted on 2015-06-27&nbsp; &quot;Your addon helped bring in over a thousand dollars in extra sales. When I updated my website version and design, the module was turned off for a while. I&#39;m glad it&#39;s back on again. Thanks again!&quot; M. Pak  Comment&nbsp;posted on 2014-08-29 21:55:04 &quot;Good module, maybe could be usefull to have a random product offer&quot;&nbsp;J. S&aacute;nchez*  Comment&nbsp;posted on 2014-03-18 07:31:35 ​&quot;Good!&quot;&nbsp;T. Aarestrup  * Feature added to the module !]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.1.15]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[59.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/595049-pprod/push-on-cart-upselling.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595049-pbig/push-on-cart-upselling.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[13654]]></id><name><![CDATA[hspointofsalepro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[RockPOS Point of Sale (POS) Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Merchandising]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Thanks to RockPOS (formerly Point of Sale Pro), now you can sell your products online and offline as well, at your stores / warehouses, exhibitions, trade conferences or via phone / chat]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaMonster]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/merchandising-prestashop-modules/13654-rockpos-point-of-sale-pos-pro.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/13654.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Thanks to RockPOS (formerly Point of Sale Pro), now you can sell your products online and offline as well, at your stores / warehouses, exhibitions, trade conferences or via phone / chat. All transactions are connected to your cloud database.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Sell your products anywhere, anytime in secondsCentralize your data, no need extra time to combine your manual orders]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.3.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/618511-pprod/rockpos-point-of-sale-pos-pro.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/618511-pbig/rockpos-point-of-sale-pos-pro.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[16535]]></id><name><![CDATA[cartabandonmentpro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Abandoned Cart Reminder Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Ordering Process]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Improve your conversion rate by 15% (and more) with abandoned carts reminder emails!]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/checkout-modules/16535-abandoned-cart-pro.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/16535.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Improve your conversion rate by 15% (and more) with abandoned carts reminder emails!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[An automatic email is sent to customers each time they add products to their shopping cart but does not purchase. It reminds and encourages them to complete the order. It&rsquo;s beneficial and easy to use!&nbsp;Automatically send one or more personalized emails to remind your customers about the contents of their cart. This helps turn abandoned carts into sales.Easily create email templates tailored to match your online store&rsquo;s theme.Also, you can now propose discounts directly via the email in order to remind your clients to finalize their purchases.&nbsp;  Abandoned Cart reminder Pro allows to easily add discounts on a product price or free shipping cost directly on the email depending on each clients cart amount.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[checkout]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.6.10]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.5.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595057-pprod/abandoned-cart-pro.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595057-pbig/abandoned-cart-pro.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[16939]]></id><name><![CDATA[seoexpert]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Expert]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Increase site traffic by landing on first page search engine results!  This SEO Expert module automatically fills in both meta tags and social media meta tags to optimize your online store for better ]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/seo-prestashop-modules/16939-seo-expert.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/16939.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Increase site traffic by landing on first page search engine results!  This SEO Expert module automatically fills in both meta tags and social media meta tags to optimize your online store for better visibility on search engines and social media platforms.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Automatically create meta tags to save over 40 hours! With the SEO Expert module:Appear on first page results on search engines like Google, Bing, Yahoo, Yandex, etc.Multiply your sales with increased web trafficImprove visibility for each language of your storeIncrease your conversions with qualified trafficDifferentiate your store with fully customized rules for product and category pagesLeverage Facebook and Twitter to acquire even more customersOptimize your online store for social media with adapted shared titles]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.1.13]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[219.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595316-pprod/seo-expert.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595316-pbig/seo-expert.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[17452]]></id><name><![CDATA[giftcards]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Gift Card]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Prices & Promotion]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Increase your sales and get more customers by offering them the chance to give the perfect gift with no risks with the Gift Card module developed by PrestaShop!&nbsp;Practical and simple, gift cards a]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/pricing-promotion-prestashop-modules/17452-gift-card.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/17452.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Increase your sales and get more customers by offering them the chance to give the perfect gift with no risks with the Gift Card module developed by PrestaShop!&nbsp;Practical and simple, gift cards are at the top of the list of the most given gifts!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This solution provides the possibility of offering gift cards for any amount you like in your store.&nbsp;Every customer can buy your gift cards to offer people the chance to come and spend them in your store.&nbsp;&nbsp;This module allows you to:&nbsp;Pick up new customers: gift card beneficiaries represent a market of new prospects you can&rsquo;t pass up!&nbsp;Increase your sales: gift card beneficiaries often spend more than the amount bought on the card.&nbsp;Encourage indecisive customers to buy: if you offer a simple gift, suitable for all targets, customers won&rsquo;t hesitate.&nbsp;&nbsp;The gift card market brings great success with consumers and its annual growth varies between 20% and 40%.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.8]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[89.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[124.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[79.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/597595-pprod/gift-card.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/597595-pbig/gift-card.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[17545]]></id><name><![CDATA[veplatform]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[VePlatform: Increase conversions from abandoned carts  ]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Advertising & Marketing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Increase your sales by adding the VePlatform&rsquo;s integrated remarketing and re-engagement apps that convert customers who abandon your site]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/advertising-marketing-newsletter-modules/17545-veplatform-increase-conversions-from-abandoned-carts.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/17545.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Increase your sales by adding the VePlatform&rsquo;s integrated remarketing and re-engagement apps that convert customers who abandon your site. &nbsp;Get connected to the VePlatform now! &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Gain access to 4 marketing apps that generate sales for tens of thousands of happy customers worldwide  &nbsp; On average we can help your business generate up to 40% in new sales per month. Website abandonment and cart abandonment are responsible for businesses only achieving up to 30% of their potential sales. 70% or 3 in 4 potential customers place your products in their basket and then abandon. VePlatform tracks all of your customers across your site and lets you deploy a series of Apps designed to win those customers back. &nbsp; You can trust our apps to:Find you new customersRetarget lost customersIncrease your online revenueIncrease customer time on your site]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[15.2.300]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/703550-pprod/veplatform-increase-conversions-from-abandoned-carts.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/703550-pbig/veplatform-increase-conversions-from-abandoned-carts.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[18167]]></id><name><![CDATA[skybankaim]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SkyBank Advanced Payment Module]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payments & Gateways]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Simple. Reliable. Secure]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/payments-gateways-prestashop-modules/18167-skybank-advanced-payment-module.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/18167.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Simple. Reliable. Secure. SkyBank has partnered with PrestaShop to provide our clients with an easy-to-use advanced payment module that provides cart owners the flexibility they need to easily accept payments online. &nbsp;Sign Up Now!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Our secure PrestaShop solution includes the ability to: &nbsp;Accept credit and debit cards as well as ACH payments (electronic check) onlineVoid transactions and issue refunds directly from your back officeAllow customers to create and manage auto-ship orders as well as update delivery frequency onlineManage, update and cancel auto-ship orders from your back officeSet the default order status by payment typeSwitch settlement modes between authorization only or sale upon orderCapture authorization only transactions directly from your back office]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/618273-pprod/skybank-advanced-payment-module.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/618273-pbig/skybank-advanced-payment-module.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[18967]]></id><name><![CDATA[livechatpro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Live Chat Pro (Responsive)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Front office features]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module allows you to chat with your visitors, track their behavior on your site in real time and view their geolocation using google maps. Many operators can chat with several users at once]]></description><author><![CDATA[ProQuality]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/18967-live-chat-pro-responsive.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/18967.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module allows you to chat with your visitors, track their behavior on your site in real time and view their geolocation using google maps. Many operators can chat with several users at once.   &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[The module DOES NOT require a monthly fee or any other fee, you buy it once and you use it without any restrictions.  A study called &ldquo;Making Proactive Chat Work&rdquo; &nbsp;found the following:&nbsp; Many online consumers want help from a live person while they are shopping online; in fact, 44% of online consumers say that having questions answered by a live person while in the middle of an online purchase is one of the most important features a Web site can offer.  An ATG Global Consumer Trend study found that 90% of customers consider live chat helpful 62% reported being more likely to purchase from the site again. A further 38% of respondents said they had made their purchase due to the chat session itself. All these attitudes were even more prevalent among respondents who bought online at least weekly. &nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.2.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/663545-pprod/live-chat-pro-responsive.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/663545-pbig/live-chat-pro-responsive.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19198]]></id><name><![CDATA[couponpop]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Coupon Pop: Convert Visitors to Paying Customers]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Advertising & Marketing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Increase Your Leads &amp; Sales Today by Offering Your Visitors a Coupon Code in Return for Following You on Social Network or for Subscribing to Your Newsletter]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/advertising-marketing-newsletter-modules/19198-coupon-pop-convert-visitors-to-paying-customers.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/19198.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Increase Your Leads &amp; Sales Today by Offering Your Visitors a Coupon Code in Return for Following You on Social Network or for Subscribing to Your Newsletter. &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[33% Average Increase in Monthly Sales25% Average Increase in Fans &amp; Followers Growth2 min Install+100,000 Happy Merchants]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.4.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/653241-pprod/coupon-pop-convert-visitors-to-paying-customers.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/653241-pbig/coupon-pop-convert-visitors-to-paying-customers.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19283]]></id><name><![CDATA[bluepay]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[BluePay Payments]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payments & Gateways]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Leading the revolution in payments, BluePay makes processing payments easy and secure]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/payments-gateways-prestashop-modules/19283-bluepay-payments.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/19283.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Leading the revolution in payments, BluePay makes processing payments easy and secure. Process credit cards, debit cards, and eCheck/ACH payments simply with BluePay!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[The BluePay Payments module makes your payments fast, easy and secure. Providing you with the highest level of security, BluePay's unique hosted payment feature reduces your PCI scope. As a PCI certified payment processor, and as one of the early implementers of tokenization, you know your payments are safe with us. The best part? This plugin is free for BluePay merchants who use the BluePay Gateway.  So what are you waiting for? Start processing payments with the BluePay/PrestaShop module today! ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/654625-pprod/bluepay-payments.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/654625-pbig/bluepay-payments.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19317]]></id><name><![CDATA[solidcommerceapp]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Solid Commerce App]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Partner Offers]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Solid Commerce -&nbsp;&nbsp;a cloud-based solution that helps multi-channel ecommerce sellers increase sales and reduce overhead costs]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/partner-offers/19317-solid-commerce-app.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/19317.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Solid Commerce -&nbsp;&nbsp;a cloud-based solution that helps multi-channel ecommerce sellers increase sales and reduce overhead costs. With powerful features: bulk listing, centralized inventory, order management, re-pricing, vendor management and shipping]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Listing Access millions of shoppers on ebay, Amazon, Rakuten and more by leveraging the inventory you already have. List, update, and revise live listings all from one place.Generate Bulk ListingsCreate Variation ListingEdit live listings&nbsp;Inventory Avoid frustrating stock-outs and overselling. With centralized inventory, you can automatically sync inventory levels across your online store and marketplaces.View inventory historySet product conditionView storage locationSupport multiple warehousesPrint barcodesManage kitting and bundling&nbsp;Orders We auto import orders, so you don&rsquo;t have to. Thanks to a direct integration with the most popular shopping carts and marketplaces, you can view, refund, and track orders from one simple screen.Print Picking Lists &amp; Packing SlipsAssign custom order statusSearch and find ordersManage returns&nbsp;Shipping Gain the functionality you need and the features you want. Print labels &amp; packing slips, scan barcodes, and mix &amp; match shipping carriers. Once an item is shipped, we will automatically send the tracking number to your marketplace or web store.Bulk print shipping labelsScan before you shipEstimate shipping costsAutomate tracking information&nbsp;Repricing Outsmart the competition and never lose the buy box again. With our Amazon repricing tool, you can set tailored options such as product condition, seller ranking, time of day, and much more.Auto-calculate Amazon feesWin the Amazon Buy BoxOption to price against the Amazon Buy BoxOption to price against FBA only&nbsp;Vendors No Inventory, No problem! Connect directly to your vendors&rsquo; inventory and automatically list products to your favorite marketplace (ebay, Amazon) and web store (Magento, Big Commerce).Auto-update based on your vendors feedSend orders to your vendors automaticallyUpdate pricing on every marketplace&nbsp;Integrated MarketplaceseBayAmazonSearsRakutenHalf.comNeweggOverstock]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[]]></tab><version><![CDATA[]]></version><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[19395]]></id><name><![CDATA[cart2cart]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cart2Cart: PrestaShop Migration Module]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Migration tools / CMS]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Cart2Cart: PrestaShop Migration Module allows to perform automated migration from 60+ e-Commerce platforms to PrestaShop or PrestaShop Cloud with no programming skills required]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/cms-prestashop-modules/19395-cart2cart-prestashop-migration-module.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/19395.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Cart2Cart: PrestaShop Migration Module allows to perform automated migration from 60+ e-Commerce platforms to PrestaShop or PrestaShop Cloud with no programming skills required. &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Free Demo migration - test how the migration works by moving a limited number of entities to PrestaShop in 10-30 min.100% uptime &nbsp;- migration process has no effect on the performance of your current store.Flexible pricing - the migration cost fully depends on the amount of transferring entities.No programming skills needed - the migration process is fully automated and requires minimum user&rsquo;s interference.Assiduous Support - professional Support team is ready to offer its help and answer any questions concerning the migration process via ticket, phone or chat.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[migration_tools]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price></module><module><id><![CDATA[19512]]></id><name><![CDATA[magnalister]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[magnalister]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marketplace & Affiliation Platforms]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Connect your Prestashop easily with eBay, Amazon &amp; Co. Upload products, import orders or synchronize stock and prices automatically]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/marketplace-prestashop-modules/19512-magnalister.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/19512.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Connect your Prestashop easily with eBay, Amazon &amp; Co. Upload products, import orders or synchronize stock and prices automatically.&nbsp; &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Sell more than ever: 78% of all online-buyer-decisions are made on marketplaces like eBay or Amazon. These are the most important distribution channels to increase your sales dramatically. Use your Prestashop in combination with the magnalister addon and make your store a distribution, inventory- and order-management-system.      &nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.3]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/666646-pprod/magnalister.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/666646-pbig/magnalister.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19532]]></id><name><![CDATA[ordercup]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[OrderCup]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Shipping & Delivery]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Streamline and automate eCommerce&nbsp;order management and shipping]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/shipping-logistics-delivery-prestashop-modules/19532-ordercup.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/19532.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Streamline and automate eCommerce&nbsp;order management and shipping. Our simple, innovative, cloud service &nbsp;integrates with leading online channels and shipping carriers, allowing you to provide better customer service while saving you time and money!&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[OrderCup simplifies and automates you entire shipping process and saves you time and money:Simple setup and configuration with the free OrderCup Module, that links to and helps confiure&nbsp;your OrderCup storeThe best commercial shipping rates with USPS and DHL, and your discounted rates with other carriers.Save time with automation,&nbsp;single and batch shipping, silent&nbsp;printing and auto-reading scale&nbsp;weights.Autnotically push&nbsp;orders in specified statuses&nbsp;in real-time to OrderCup.Value-added features including returns, shipping insurance, free global address verification, and&nbsp;free supplies and pickups for some&nbsp;carriers.Access to the comprehensive shipping functionality. For more visit http://www.ordercup.com/products/features.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/666656-pprod/ordercup.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/666656-pbig/ordercup.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19626]]></id><name><![CDATA[cardpaysolutions]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cardpay Solutions]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payments & Gateways]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Fast, reliable, and secure payment processing service for both traditional and high-risk merchants.&nbsp; Accept all major credit cards (Visa, MasterCard, American Express, Discover, JCB, and Diners)]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/payments-gateways-prestashop-modules/19626-cardpay-solutions.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/19626.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Fast, reliable, and secure payment processing service for both traditional and high-risk merchants.&nbsp; Accept all major credit cards (Visa, MasterCard, American Express, Discover, JCB, and Diners).&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Rates starting as low as 1.89% + $0.23 and next day funding available for low-risk merchant types.&nbsp; Our easy online application and fast approval allows you to get up and running quickly!&nbsp; Two simple pricing plans available to meet your needs:Basic Plan:&nbsp; 2.90% + $0.30 - No Monthly FeePro Plan:&nbsp; 1.89% + $0.23 - $19.95/month We are able to approve both traditional e-commerce merchants as well as those that fall into high-risk categories, such as:Adult Productse-Cigarettes &amp; VaporizersSupplements &amp; NutraceuticalsDiet ProgramsPC Technical Supportand many more...]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/669007-pprod/cardpay-solutions.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/669007-pbig/cardpay-solutions.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19784]]></id><name><![CDATA[luckyorange]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Lucky Orange]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Analytics & Stats]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Instantly identify the pain points in your checkout process, and find out why 99% of your visitors never become&nbsp;customers]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/analytics-stats-prestashop-modules/19784-lucky-orange.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/19784.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Instantly identify the pain points in your checkout process, and find out why 99% of your visitors never become&nbsp;customers.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Do you know why your visitors don&#39;t convert?  Lucky Orange&nbsp;lets&nbsp;you watch movies of how your actual visitors interacted with your store. See how they view products, add items to the shopping cart, and abandon forms so you can&nbsp;discover the true reasons your visitors aren&#39;t converting.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Best Module Traffic"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/awards-traffic.png]]></badge><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/673345-pprod/lucky-orange.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/673345-pbig/lucky-orange.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19927]]></id><name><![CDATA[quotation]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Online Quotation]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Prices & Promotion]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Allow customers to ask for a quote in your online shop! With the Online quotation module, create a made-to-measure form so your customers can ask for an estimate for the products they are interested i]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/pricing-promotion-prestashop-modules/19927-online-quotation.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/19927.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Allow customers to ask for a quote in your online shop! With the Online quotation module, create a made-to-measure form so your customers can ask for an estimate for the products they are interested in and you pick up all the information you needed to create an estimate.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increase the conversion rate of your shop by making an attractive offer by estimateIncrease the average shopping cart by encouraging your customers to buy more products they hadn&rsquo;t planned toAllow your customers to order personalised items using offers by estimateOptimise your shop&rsquo;s reassurance and customer satisfaction by advising your customers using estimates&nbsp; Make a personalised study and follow-up of every estimate request you receive. Send your proposal to your customer, who can turn the estimate into an order with a single click. &nbsp; Our tip: A few days after sending the estimate, send a reminder e-mail using the &ldquo;Abandoned Cart Reminder Pro&rdquo; module&nbsp; &nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.17]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[174.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[109.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/676340-pprod/online-quotation.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/676340-pbig/online-quotation.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19946]]></id><name><![CDATA[marketing360]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Marketing 360®]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Advertising & Marketing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Get a FREE Demo &amp; Plans and Pricing! Marketing 360&reg; is the #1 marketing platform&trade; in the world]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/advertising-marketing-newsletter-modules/19946-marketing-360.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/19946.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Get a FREE Demo &amp; Plans and Pricing! Marketing 360&reg; is the #1 marketing platform&trade; in the world. Leverage world-class marketing software, services and the best website designs&nbsp;for generating sales through a single, powerful, intelligent platform.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[The Marketing 360&reg; platform is an intelligent combination of digital marketing software and dedicated marketing services. It&#39;s extremely affordable, powerful and full-service. There&#39;s simply nothing else like it.&nbsp; It&#39;s everything you need to generate sales and grow your brand.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Best Module Traffic"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/awards-traffic.png]]></badge><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/677100-pprod/marketing-360.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/677100-pbig/marketing-360.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19991]]></id><name><![CDATA[mercury]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Mercury Payment Systems]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payments & Gateways]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[&nbsp;MercuryPay&reg; - Credit Card Processing- Payment Processing Your Way &nbsp;]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/payments-gateways-prestashop-modules/19991-mercury-payment-systems.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/19991.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[&nbsp;MercuryPay&reg; - Credit Card Processing- Payment Processing Your Way &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[&nbsp;MercuryPay&reg; - Credit Card ProcessingPayment Processing Your Way Get fast, reliable, and secure transactions with MercuryPay&reg;, Mercury&rsquo;s award-winning payment processing. Accept the most common payment types and card brands, and enjoy high reliability, speedy funding, promotional payment options, and instant transaction viewing.  &bull; Seamless integration with the POS of your choice&nbsp; &bull; Friendly 24/7 support from U.S. based POS experts &bull; Super-fast credit, debit, gift, mobile and EBT transaction approvals &bull; Free gift and store card transactions with promotional features &bull; Rigorous card data security with breach protection assistance&nbsp; &nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[0.3.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.17]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/688796-pprod/mercury-payment-systems.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/688796-pbig/mercury-payment-systems.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[20242]]></id><name><![CDATA[bridgeconnector]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Bridge Connector for Store Manager]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Quick / Mass Edit]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Bridge Connector allows you to connect Store Manager application to PrestaShop Cloud and perform advanced data update and input (import, export, mass edit, etc)]]></description><author><![CDATA[eMagicOne]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/bulk-update-prestashop-modules/20242-bridge-connector-for-store-manager.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/20242.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Bridge Connector allows you to connect Store Manager application to PrestaShop Cloud and perform advanced data update and input (import, export, mass edit, etc). Should be used with Store Manager desktop application]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Merchants will get access to their&nbsp;PrestaShop Cloud database with the help of Store Manager and perform the following operations: - Work with categories and products on a single page - no reload required; - Change prices of multiple products at the same time (perfect for sales!); - Create product features and combinations in bulk; - Upload multiple images simultaneously (drag and drop directly onto the browser); - Quickly update your inventory, manage stock levels, warehouses, and stock movements; - Import products (including virtual), specific prices, multi-features, attribute values, customized fields, and combinations; - Import products from csv, txt, xml, xls/xslx (Excel), ods (OpenOffice). No file requirements - all missing data can be applied on the fly; - Import customers with passwords exported from another PrestaShop installation (requires additional assistance); - Create orders with a POS and process them in bulk (e.g. change status for multiple orders at once); - Use store diagnostics to fix missing or broken images; - Take advantage of powerful reporting features; - Manage multiple PrestaShop installations and shops with one back-office; - Work offline - all changes will be applied when you reconnect.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[quick_bulk_update]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.3]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/691041-pprod/bridge-connector-for-store-manager.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/691041-pbig/bridge-connector-for-store-manager.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[20301]]></id><name><![CDATA[optimalpayment]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Optimal Payments]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payments & Gateways]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Optimal Payments makes several million transactions each day with Secure and speedy]]></description><author><![CDATA[Zedrox]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/payments-gateways-prestashop-modules/20301-optimal-payments.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/20301.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Optimal Payments makes several million transactions each day with Secure and speedy. It supports all major forms of credit card transactions including Visa &reg;, MasterCard &reg;, American Express &reg;, Discover &reg;, Diners Club &reg; and JCB &reg;. &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Optimal Payments basic principle is to provide secure payments.As an internationally-oriented Payment Service Provider Optimal Payments Payments has a lot to offer. Why choose Optimal Payments Payment gateway: 1)Quick and easy to use plugin 2)Safe and reliable payment system 3)Wide offering of payment options 4)Real-time status of payments 5)Accept real time payment without leaving your website. &nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.6.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/692431-pprod/optimal-payments.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/692431-pbig/optimal-payments.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[20306]]></id><name><![CDATA[koongoconnector]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Koongo - Feed & Affiliate Marketing Tool]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Advertising & Marketing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Koongo is Feed and Affiliate Marketing Tool that allows integration of electronic stores with 500+ product aggregators, affiliate networks and selling channels worldwide]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/advertising-marketing-newsletter-modules/20306-koongo-feed-affiliate-marketing-tool.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/20306.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Koongo is Feed and Affiliate Marketing Tool that allows integration of electronic stores with 500+ product aggregators, affiliate networks and selling channels worldwide.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Connect with 500+ selling channels and affiliate networks worldwide!Automate product feed export and keep feeds always up-to-date!Increase your visibility and revenues by up to 25%!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.1.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[20541]]></id><name><![CDATA[djtalbrazilianregister]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Brazilian Registration]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Front office features]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module adds the optional or obligatory fields of CPF, CNPJ, IE and RG in the registration form of your online store]]></description><author><![CDATA[BM Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/20541-brazilian-registration.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/20541.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module adds the optional or obligatory fields of CPF, CNPJ, IE and RG in the registration form of your online store. It also searches and fills the client’s address with the CEP number and has a mask for the Brazilian phone number pattern.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[The storeowner has total control over the requested information in the registration form. CPF and CNPJ  can be configured as obligatory fields. The module will verify if the informed CPF or the CNPJ are correct. This information should be trustworthy for the issue of the Brazilian Nota Fiscal. The CEP can be used to obtain the client’s address. For clients that don’t know their CEP there is an option for the storeowner to display a “I don’t know my CEP” button. This will redirect the customer to Correios website to get help. ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[34.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[24.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/704295-pprod/brazilian-registration.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/704295-pbig/brazilian-registration.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[20656]]></id><name><![CDATA[inmotion]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Inmotion]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Services]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[InMotion Hosting now offers FREE solid-state drives with all of our shared hosting plans, and Prestashop comes pre-installed]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/services/20656-inmotion.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/20656.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[InMotion Hosting now offers FREE solid-state drives with all of our shared hosting plans, and Prestashop comes pre-installed. Our platform allows you to start building a high-performance web store with no delays. With our fully scalable solutions and award-winning, 24/7, US based support team, InMotion Hosting will always be there for you as you e-commerce business grows.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[At InMotion Hosting, we love PrestaShop! We have been providing professional grade web hosting solutions since 2001; offering Shared, VPS, Dedicated, and Commercial Class solutions for virtually every application. With hundreds of PrestaShop related tutorials and articles, InMotion Hosting offers a dedicated PrestaShop Education Center, aimed at giving users a resource for the installation and customization of PrestaShop and our hosting platform. Our in house support staffs have been professionally trained to properly handle all your PrestaShop related questions and concerns. InMotion Hosting has been a 3 Star Certified Hosting Provider since 2003 and has an A+ rating with the Better Business Bureau. As a recommended PrestaShop Hosting provider, we offer 1 Click Installations via Softaculous. PrestaShop merchants enjoy 30% off as well as FREE domains!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[]]></tab><version><![CDATA[]]></version><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[20659]]></id><name><![CDATA[webhostinghub]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[WebHostingHub]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Services]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[WebHostingHub offers you the easiest way to get your website and ecommerce presence online at a fraction of the cost of other providers]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/services/20659-webhostinghub.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/20659.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[WebHostingHub offers you the easiest way to get your website and ecommerce presence online at a fraction of the cost of other providers. With 24/7/365 US Based Support, unlimited resources, and a 1-Click installation of PrestaShop, WebHostingHub will be able to get you up and running within minutes!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Whether you are new to creating a web site or an advanced web master, WebHostingHub offers a choice for everyone. With the abundant amount of tools and resources in place, as well as 24/7 US support, WebHostingHub will allow you to get your web site up quickly and effectively without the painstakingly long hours of programming and coding.&nbsp; We also offer an extensive education channel, filled with PrestaShop tutorials and resources for everyone to reference.&nbsp; Find out today why&nbsp;WebHostingHub is one of the best web hosting solutions around. We&rsquo;ve secured you an exclusive deal through PrestaShop.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[]]></tab><version><![CDATA[]]></version><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[20682]]></id><name><![CDATA[arukereso]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Arukereso]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marketplace & Affiliation Platforms]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module handles the product export (CSV) and allows you to add the Arukereso trusted shop code to your PrestaShop without having to touch the code]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/marketplace-prestashop-modules/20682-arukereso.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/20682.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module handles the product export (CSV) and allows you to add the Arukereso trusted shop code to your PrestaShop without having to touch the code.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Export products to Arukereso and easily integrate the checkout tracking to your system.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.6.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[34.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[24.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/708869-pprod/arukereso.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/708869-pbig/arukereso.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[20874]]></id><name><![CDATA[export2bizrate]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Bizrate - Export + Advanced Filters]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Smart shopping]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Bizrate makes comparison shopping easy with Product Reviews, Merchant Ratings, Deal Alerts & Coupons]]></description><author><![CDATA[Prestalia]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/comparison-shopping-prestashop/20874-bizrate-export-advanced-filters.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/20874.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Bizrate makes comparison shopping easy with Product Reviews, Merchant Ratings, Deal Alerts & Coupons. Compare Prices & Read Reviews on Top Brands in Home & Garden, Clothing & Accessories, Sports & Outdoors, Electronics & More!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increase your conversion rate and your earningsIncrease your traffic to your storeIncrease the visibility of your site and your productsThanks to the various filters you can choose exactly which product and export to optimize your investment, avoiding the dispersion of the budget and maximizing return on investment.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[smart_shopping]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/719600-pprod/bizrate-export-advanced-filters.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/719600-pbig/bizrate-export-advanced-filters.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[20954]]></id><name><![CDATA[getresponse]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[GetResponse]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Advertising & Marketing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Your e-commerce store is the perfect tool for building a profitable email marketing list. Email marketing is the perfect way to maximize your sales]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/advertising-marketing-newsletter-modules/20954-getresponse.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/20954.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Your e-commerce store is the perfect tool for building a profitable email marketing list. Email marketing is the perfect way to maximize your sales. Both create a powerful solution that will strengthen customer relationships and increase your ROI.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[&nbsp;With the GetResponse PrestaShop integration, you can:Automatically synchronize your contacts and boost your email marketing listSegment your audience according to the types of products they buyAdd contacts to relevant email marketing campaignsSend your customers offers tailored to their needsUse web forms to invite visitors to subscribe to seasonal promotions, special offers, or latest newsChoose from a variety of web form templates that match your businessConsolidate your contacts and manage everything from one platform&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.6.2]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.3]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[21273]]></id><name><![CDATA[pqeasypost]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Easy Post Pro (DHL, UPS, Colis Privé, Royal Mail, etc.)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Shipping & Delivery]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module allows you to significaly increase the speed of your shipping process by integrating EasyPost]]></description><author><![CDATA[ProQuality]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/shipping-logistics-delivery-prestashop-modules/21273-easy-post-pro-dhl-ups-colis-prive-royal-mail-etc.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/21273.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module allows you to significaly increase the speed of your shipping process by integrating EasyPost.com API (Application Programming Interface) into PrestaShop and printing your shipping labels fast and easy.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[We all know that in order to run a successful business you have to optimize it and automatize it as much as possible, this module allows you to do that by increasing the shipping process by 70%.   Think of how long it takes to receive an order from your customers, process the order by adding the products to the package, then connect to your shipping carrier`s software and manually insert the customer information, parcel information and delivery address for the order, for each order at a time. This is very time consuming and it`s very easy to make mistakes because you have a lot of data to process.  With this module all of this is done automatically via the API (Application Programming Interface) that connects the orders section in prestashop with the carrier and instantly sends the information to the carrier, then prints the shipping label which is then slicked to the package. The module supports the most important carriers in the world.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[59.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/722263-pprod/easy-post-pro-dhl-ups-colis-prive-royal-mail-etc.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/722263-pbig/easy-post-pro-dhl-ups-colis-prive-royal-mail-etc.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21310]]></id><name><![CDATA[djtalkomerci]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Brazilian Payment by Rede Card - Komerci]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payments & Gateways]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Receive credit card payments from all over the world in your Prestashop online store with “Komerci 4 Prestashop By DJTAL”. This module integrates Komerci, the e-commerce payment solution of REDE]]></description><author><![CDATA[BM Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/payments-gateways-prestashop-modules/21310-brazilian-payment-by-rede-card-komerci.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/21310.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Receive credit card payments from all over the world in your Prestashop online store with “Komerci 4 Prestashop By DJTAL”. This module integrates Komerci, the e-commerce payment solution of REDE.    ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[REDE is one of the biggest and more trusted Brazilian brands of credit card machines. Make payment available on your online shopping business for MasterCard®, Visa, Diners Club International and, as an exclusivity of Komerci, Hiper and Hipercard. Your clients can pay in 12 monthly installments with their credit card, and enjoy the checkout inside the Prestashop store.  The “Komerci 4 Prestashop By DJTAL” grants full access and compatibility of your Prestashop store with Komerci, the e-commerce payment solution of REDE.Authorization with the withholding of captureReal-time approval of transactionsAvailability of payments in 12 monthly installments with credit cardCheckout with no site redirectionFull integration with the system and online store of PrestashopSecurityFraud risk tracking – Using our tool with Clearsale technology you can track all the transaction process and have warnings of all fraud risks as they happen.AVS (Confirmation of the client’s data on time) – Confirmation of the exactitude between the identification and address data in the visitor’s registration and in the credit card billing information.International SecureCode – Accept with the same security credit cards from all over the world.  Withholding Capture Gain time to analyze your sales. Reserve capture process until the cardholder billing time limit. You will have a 15 days deadline to analyze, authorize and deliver your product or service.   Lowest Cost Komerci is a payment gateway that dismisses third-party processors. This way you will not pay tuitions, only a tax over each sale.   Checkout inside Prestashop Your Prestashop cart will work normally, as you have set it for your e-commerce website, without website redirection.   Credit Cards Offer more payment options. With “Komerci 4 Prestashop By DJTAL” your client can pay with Hiper and Hipercard, besides MasterCard®, Visa and Diners Club International.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[64.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/722882-pprod/brazilian-payment-by-rede-card-komerci.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/722882-pbig/brazilian-payment-by-rede-card-komerci.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21328]]></id><name><![CDATA[djtalrastreamento]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Brazilian Correios Tracking]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Shipping & Delivery]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[With the “Brazilian Correios Tracking” module you and your client will have total agility and comfort to track the orders of your Prestashop online store in Brazil]]></description><author><![CDATA[BM Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/shipping-logistics-delivery-prestashop-modules/21328-brazilian-correios-tracking.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/21328.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[With the “Brazilian Correios Tracking” module you and your client will have total agility and comfort to track the orders of your Prestashop online store in Brazil. Save time for your customer service  ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This product tracking module is so easy for your customer that he will not need you ever again to track his order.  Quick list of open orders  The module adds a window for tracking in all of the pages of the website and its location on each page is controlled by you the storeowner. Logged-in clients on your online store will see the Quick Tracking List. In it, they will have an automatic list with all of their open orders and their respective object codes.  One click product tracking The listed object codes are direct links to the Correios table with the full tracking information for that order. No copy paste, only one click. This way to get to the tracking table is also available for the storeowner in Prestashop’s dashboard, in the normal session to manage orders.  Less customer service, more satisfied customers Your customer service people can do way more than answer emails about where the client order is at the moment, each moment, every day until it arrives. With the “Brazilian Correios Tracking” module as soon as the client enters the site to make the question, he will see the Quick Tracking List with all of the open orders listed and the object codes ready to be clicked.  Practicality As soon as the logged in client enters the site in any page, he/she will see the window listing all his open orders with the object codes as links to the tracking.  Agility Client and storeowner access the Correios tracking table with only one click.  Simplicity The integration with the dashboard of Prestashop is simple. The only chande is that the object codes in your normal list of open orders are now links.  Tranquility More clients doing their own product tracking with ease means more satisfied shoppers and less workload for your customer service people. Now you can focus on what’s really important.  ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[34.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[24.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/723224-pprod/brazilian-correios-tracking.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/723224-pbig/brazilian-correios-tracking.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21329]]></id><name><![CDATA[xpsshipmulticarriershipping]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[XPS Ship - Multi-carrier Shipping]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Shipping & Delivery]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[A free multi-carrier shipping solution (regardless of your shipping volume), XPS Ship streamlines your order fulfillment. Orders placed on your PrestaShop website and marketplaces (E.G]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/shipping-logistics-delivery-prestashop-modules/21329-xps-ship-multi-carrier-shipping.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/21329.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[A free multi-carrier shipping solution (regardless of your shipping volume), XPS Ship streamlines your order fulfillment. Orders placed on your PrestaShop website and marketplaces (E.G. Amazon, eBay, etc.) are automatically populated into XPS, enabling you to efficiently generate shipping labels for all the major carriers, including USPS, DHL, FedEx, and UPS. You&rsquo;ll receive discounts on domestic and international shipping and will have access to live customer service.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Free multi-carrier shipping solution with no limitations on shipments.Single user interface enabling label generation for USPS, FedEx, UPS and DHL&hellip; all from a single screen.Ship orders one-by-one or multiple at a time using BATCH functionality.Email notifications are automatically sent to your customers with tracking information for their order.Integration with marketplaces (E.G. Amazon, eBay, Etsy, etc.) making fulfillment of these orders as easy as those from PrestaShop.LIVE CUSTOMER SERVICE: 1-800-881-0288 / info@xpsship.com.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[]]></version><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/723362-pprod/xps-ship-multi-carrier-shipping.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/723362-pbig/xps-ship-multi-carrier-shipping.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21381]]></id><name><![CDATA[djtalclearsalestart]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Anti-Fraud ClearSale Start]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payment Security]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The “Anti-Fraud ClearSale Start” module provides information so you can make sales decisions with safety, thanks to the ClearSale technology]]></description><author><![CDATA[BM Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/secure-payment-prestashop-modules/21381-anti-fraud-clearsale-start.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/21381.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The “Anti-Fraud ClearSale Start” module provides information so you can make sales decisions with safety, thanks to the ClearSale technology. Clarify your doubts about suspicious orders and send merchandise with security and peace of mind. ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[On-demand instant verification of the order’s fraud risk. This is done, directly on the Prestashop dashboard, crossing the client’s data filled by the storeowner with those that the system can verify through ClearSale technology. Identification, address, credit card number and the purchase value are some of the information that can be verified on a history level, exactitude or authenticity of the cardholder’s documents.Integration of the ClearSale system, Start, with your Prestashp online store.Smart verification form with dynamic filling inside the Order Status section.Instant verification of order and client data.On-demand verification. You contract ClearSale for a pack of verifications, this means that you will pay in a per query basis and can use that credit only for the really suspicious orders]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payment_security]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/724625-pprod/anti-fraud-clearsale-start.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/724625-pbig/anti-fraud-clearsale-start.jpg]]></big></cover></module></modules>